<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="6"><![CDATA[Canada]]></country>
<locale id="4"><![CDATA[Ontario]]></locale>
<city id="20"><![CDATA[Toronto]]></city>
<venue id="482"><![CDATA[Molson Amphitheatre]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Molson+Amphitheatre</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Friday, August 15, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>657</previousshow>
<nextshow>659</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Grizzly Bear]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="3" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="4" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="5" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="6" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="7" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="8" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="9" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="10" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="11" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="12" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="13" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="14" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="15" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="16" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="56"><![CDATA[Like Spinning Plates]]></track>
<track num="19" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="20" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="21" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="22" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="24" id="16"><![CDATA[Planet Telex]]></track>
<track num="25" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cosplusisin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[aryall]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[usher]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[punkerpaul]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jonnymark]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tapeworm]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[miel]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[killymagee]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[qwiggles2]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Winfield]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[slint]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[nicopop]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rdiohd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Psycho]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cme314]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Linkletter]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jlowry]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Idaa]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neo-jason]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[nude88]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Citizen_insane]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Citizen_insane]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="Andrew" timestamp="4:53 PM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[I was at both this show and the Cleveland 8/4 show (which was probably the best night of my life), but aside from having much better seats in cleveland there were several technical difficulties throughout the night, (phil's snares not on for the first verse of 15 step, Jonnys guitar on the wrong settings for parts of optimistic and the start of planet telex, rhodes trouble on morning bell) and since technicians had to keep coming out to fix things it sort of personally distracted me from being caught up in some of the songs, however they remained very professional and definately got it together by the end of the night to deliver 2 incredible sets of encores. Talk show host was even better live than the recording ]]></comment>
<comment author="adam" timestamp="2:24 PM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[it was the best experience of my life

everything just seemed to go perfect

highlights: reckoner played 2nd, wolf, jigsaw, cutw, talk show host]]></comment>
<comment author="Darrin" timestamp="10:03 AM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[I've seen Radiohead 8 times since The Bends show at Varsity Arena. Like every show, I walked away thinking it was in the top 3 shows I've ever seen. I now have 8 Radiohead shows in my top 3 shows of all time. Every song from In Rainbows was played tonight. I have faith that one day they'll play Lurgee again.]]></comment>
<comment author="NotCordelia" timestamp="9:43 AM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[This show was completely satisfying. Radiohead calmly surpassed all of the hype and build-up to prove once again that they are, indeed, the best band in the world. I'm sure it's been this way on every stop of the tour, and personally I find it very comforting to know that such large numbers of people are unified by these guys. Their writing and playing are the stuff musical dreams are made of. In fact, the experience of seeing them live has a distinct dream-like feel to it. The show was magical, they played all 10 tracks of In Rainbows, not ONE of their three mega-hits, and I couldn't conjure a complaint if I tried.]]></comment>
<comment author="jjppp777" timestamp="7:47 AM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[Of all the shows on this leg of the tour, this is the only setlist I've seen on here that I would've preferred to the one I got (I was at Lollapalooza 8/1/08). I guess the National Anthem got skipped, but Planet Telex, Street Spirit, Climbing Up the Walls, Wolf at the Door, Spinning Plates, and freakin TALK SHOW HOST?!!??? you guys were very lucky, I'm a little jealous]]></comment>
<comment author="Dan S" timestamp="12:39 AM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[My first time seeing them and it was amazing, especially standing in front of the stage in the 100 section. I'm jealous the previous show (which I think has had the best setlist thus far on the tour; you lucky bastards) got BOTH How to Disappear Completely AND Exit Music, but I'll live. 

Two or three rainbows were seen in the distance as the Grizzly Bears set was coming to a close.

It rained off and on throughout the show. Pyramid Song was beautiful, No Surprises and Talk Show Host were pleasant surprises, even if I'm not a big fan of the latter, and Climbing Up the Walls was delightful.

Thom was having mic problems during Morning Bell (I think), which were fixed on the double.

The band seemed very appreciative which is always nice to see, and the crowd always tried to one up it. Throughout the whole show, the songs constantly entertained, so there wasn't one weak moment, even if some of the bigger singles were left off the set. Can't wait to see them again.]]></comment>
<comment author="Rapha" timestamp="12:00 AM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[Like the other guy said, they left out all their hit radio raped songs and this was probably the best concert I have ever been to. The rain sucked. Shouldn't have warn my nice simple shoes. Mud everywhere in the lawns. Was gross but good times! They sound tighter than ever. The visuals were amazing!]]></comment>
<comment author="punker" timestamp="11:18 PM [PST], Friday, August 15, 2008"><![CDATA[Awesome! Totally Awesome! I agree I was looking for more of the classics,but the mix of the old and new had a great flow. Seeing In Rainbows performed live I think we are witnessing more classics to come. Many people leaving the venue
said this was the best concert they have seen. Other than Floyd I have to agree.]]></comment>
<comment author="chris" timestamp="10:51 PM [PST], Friday, August 15, 2008"><![CDATA[having been a witness to several shows over the past 15 years, I feel like the band has taken a step to a new level.  the arsenal is so complete, that leaving out heavy hitters such as Android, Just and Karma in a city like Toronto (with great rhead history) speaks volumes.  I thought I wanted to hear those songs.......but did not need them.  Great job.  ]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=658]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
