<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="1"><![CDATA[California]]></locale>
<city id="13"><![CDATA[Santa Barbara]]></city>
<venue id="94"><![CDATA[Santa Barbara Bowl]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Santa+Barbara+Bowl</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Thursday, August 28, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>664</previousshow>
<nextshow>666</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="2" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="3" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="4" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="5" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="6" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="7" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="8" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="9" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="10" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="11" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="12" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="13" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="14" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="15" id="17"><![CDATA[The Bends]]></track>
<track num="16" id="2"><![CDATA[Karma Police]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="155"><![CDATA[Cymbal Rush]]></track>
<track num="19" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="20" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="21" id="162"><![CDATA[Go Slowly]]></track>
<track num="22" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="24" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="25" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Covebum]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jessica]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[debaser]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Tabooty]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Bort]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neekole]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[wierdfishee]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lucky Schnauzer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ATLFalconsFAN]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[BellyofaWhale]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dymo23]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pure]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[MattHeckman]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mrpoptop]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Kid Julian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[redsoxfaan3]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jrsdthird]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cygnus7]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[onablankshore9]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dennisdster]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[diztorted]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chaos_lynn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[markcharlessmith]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[michaelmirra]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rbarthjr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rhfans]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="BellyofaWhale" timestamp="9:03 AM [PST], Friday, September 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Great great show! Beautiful, intimate venue. I will definitely do whatever I can to see Radiohead at this venue in the future. There isn't a bad seat in the house. It was my third show in five days and the band seemed in very high spirits, excited to finish and celebrate the tour. It was nice to hear Thom thank everybody at the end of Videotape and he was generally talkative, especially compared to the Hollywood Bowl shows. When Thom came out in his red pants and they opened with Reckoner, I knew we were in for a treat. Talk Show Host was epic, The Bends rocked with the best light show of any song I saw on the tour, Cymbal Rush was beautiful, and Videotape was especially resonate with this being the end of the major tour and my last show of the tour. But, really, every song was magic (15 Step, Jigsaw, Karma Police singalong, Bodysnatchers, Idioteque, everything). Great show. I'm still high from it weeks later (thanks to the NPR recording!) Till next tour...]]></comment>
<comment author="pumkinshakerMike" timestamp="4:51 PM [PST], Tuesday, September 09, 2008"><![CDATA[You can also stream it here: 
http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=94315732

The sound is perfect!]]></comment>
<comment author="pzy" timestamp="1:42 PM [PST], Tuesday, September 09, 2008"><![CDATA[Audio of the entire show from NPR, sounds fantastic:

http://podcastdownload.npr.org/anon.npr-podcasts/podcast/510253/94387347/npr_94387347.mp3]]></comment>
<comment author="Jeff Moehlis" timestamp="6:13 PM [PST], Monday, September 01, 2008"><![CDATA[It was an awesome show!  Here is the link to a review of the concert I wrote for noozhawk.com, a Santa Barbara online newspaper.

http://www.noozhawk.com/noozhawk/article/0831_radiohead_lights_up_the_county_bowl_with_sights_and_sound/]]></comment>
<comment author="mel" timestamp="6:49 PM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[Eric:  i was at the vancouver show, 3rd time seeing them. somehow i ended up in the front row to the right, by johnny, but the crowd was so nuts i had to get pulled out during the fourth song. still can't believe that happened, but at least i was there for a little bit (that's what i'm trying to tell myself). still was an amazing show, as always, but seeing the webcast without any problems would've made it even better. oh well, hopefully it will be posted somewhere soon... ]]></comment>
<comment author="Eric Con Queso" timestamp="1:58 PM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[Yup, I had problems watching the webcast as well.  Too bad too, because I was able to see the last 4-5 songs and what I saw was steller.  Hoping they post it somewhere soon!
I saw them in Seattle last week and the video really couldn't capture the complete awesomeness of the stage however.  But having the video is better than nothing I'll say.]]></comment>
<comment author="Roy McLean" timestamp="11:16 AM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[Thank you Radiohead for a mindblowing tour and an awesome webcast.  Here's to another visit next year.]]></comment>
<comment author="mike" timestamp="8:33 AM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[This was by far the most acoustically friendly and environmentally sustaintable venue I have ever visited.  Just to give you an idea of what the santa barabara bowl is like: there are 4-way stop signs leading up to the amphitheater (which everyone respects); the venue is nestled in a hilly neighborhood at the intersection of two streets.  You can park in the high school parking lot for $7...and all the locals will tell you that paying for parking is a racket since you can just park for free on any of the side streets.  They checked my backpack by giving me a ticket stub with a number on it- and there was hardly a line to claim it afterward!  I've seen Radiohead about 20 times dating from 1997, and never at a show that had less than 25,000 people.  The SB Bowl can't seat more than 5,000 people--what an amazing treat!  Idioteque was CRazY and EIIRP was wonderful.  Thank you thank you!]]></comment>
<comment author="Jami" timestamp="7:40 AM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[Wow.  My head is still buzzing ten hours after that show last night.  I finally got to see the band play live and they did not disappoint at the SB Bowl.  I don't know that there was a cooler venue for these guys on their whole tour; halfway up the bowl i was still only about 250 yards from the stage.  the set was killer, the band was on point, and all the people around me were cool when i sparked all three of my mood enhancers.  it was a great set; the lights and screens were really cool.  stay frosty radiohead.  i will certainly go out of my way to catch you again.]]></comment>
<comment author="David" timestamp="6:40 AM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[The radio chatter during "The National Anthem" does change every night. Jonny Greewnood uses a radio and finds the right stations (usually political talk radio) before the gig...

At least that's what I've always heard! =)]]></comment>
<comment author="velly" timestamp="1:27 AM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[andrew:  it's a live radio that's tuned each day to a couple different local stations.  jonny switches thru them and processes the signal thru delay effects
]]></comment>
<comment author="david" timestamp="12:27 AM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[sublime transcendent direct intense beautiful dark warm... an amazing transmission.  caught them in sf and la and tonight.  really loved tonight.  hoping they come back soon.]]></comment>
<comment author="Mel" timestamp="10:42 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Did anyone else have any massive problems trying to watch the webcast? It kept cutting out the whole time, no consistent sound or image. It was very upsetting, and I'm hoping it will be posted somewhere else to watch at a later time? Any thoughts?]]></comment>
<comment author="Zach" timestamp="10:12 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Thank you for the amazing tour Radiohead.  You did an outstanding job.  This show was spot on!  Nothing was wrong.  Although I did like Mansfield better.  But this was also a 20 out of 10!  

Amazing!  Now let's look forward to an other set of songs (8th album) that we can enjoy live!  ]]></comment>
<comment author="clay" timestamp="9:59 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[changes nightly.  it's live sampling from a local radio station (so shows overseas often have intros in other languages).]]></comment>
<comment author="berga52" timestamp="9:41 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Thank you Radiohead for webcasting this and for the Mansfield show. ]]></comment>
<comment author="brn." timestamp="9:33 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Its not a sample, its a portable radio that Jonny uses to tune into local radio stations i believe.  Because of this it is different every show]]></comment>
<comment author="Ed" timestamp="9:33 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Thom, after Paranoid Android:

"I didn't mean it about the surgeon...whatever you want, you know..."

HE'S GONE MENTAL!!!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="PumkinshakerMike" timestamp="9:27 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Thom right before Paranoid Android: "This is for anyone who had surgery: You're gonna be dead soon. It's all going south, brother." 

Friggin hilarious!]]></comment>
<comment author="Ed" timestamp="9:27 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Thom is a nut, Paranoid Android intro tonight:

"This is for anyone who's haveing sugery...you're gonna be dead soon...it's all going downhill, brother..."

LOLOLOL

Andrew, I believe it changes nightly, via Jonny's portable radio.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=665]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
