<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="28"><![CDATA[Virginia]]></locale>
<city id="260"><![CDATA[Bristow]]></city>
<venue id="471"><![CDATA[Nissan Pavillion at Stone Ridge]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Nissan+Pavillion+at+Stone+Ridge</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Sunday, May 11, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="11"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Spring) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>623</previousshow>
<nextshow>625</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Liars]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="2" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="3" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="4" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="5" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="6" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="7" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="8" id="89"><![CDATA[Myxomatosis]]></track>
<track num="9" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="10" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="11" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="12" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="13" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="14" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="15" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="16" id="156"><![CDATA[Bangers and Mash]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="56"><![CDATA[Like Spinning Plates]]></track>
<track num="19" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="20" id="2"><![CDATA[Karma Police]]></track>
<track num="21" id="162"><![CDATA[Go Slowly]]></track>
<track num="22" id="16"><![CDATA[Planet Telex]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="19"><![CDATA[Fake Plastic Trees]]></track>
<track num="24" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="25" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rdtyphn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[crp640]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tenacious z]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[CocoacabanaBoy]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardhead]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fradleybox]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[foraminute10]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[noel1948]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[buddha]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[annie33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[little_rowboat]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pxichk]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bobcat34]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bsimms]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[OMS]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[inourhands]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[swvl]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hawkiize]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cbbjr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[willysquared]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dingus]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[leifdog222]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[andrewudin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[koubiak]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[DCno10]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pure]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blink_your_eyes]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[occurs]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[grobie1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[trojanpony]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[geeveebee]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blazak]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thingsfallapart]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bobw@wrnr.com]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sweetcell]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Kris]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sometimesnj]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rdiohd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lanora]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[grobie07]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[goTOsleep]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bengrobe1]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[Soundcheck included:<br><a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=75">2+2=5</a><br /><a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=157">Jigsaw Falling Into Place</a><br /><a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=165">Down Is The New Up</a><br /><a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=22">Just</a><br /><a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=166">All I Need</a><br /><a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=56">Like Spinning Plates</a><br />]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="goTOsleep" timestamp="7:06 AM [PST], Monday, October 20, 2008"><![CDATA[Having heard all about the light show before heading to the show I thought I knew what to expect..then I was wrong and was blown away even more than I expected..Having seats I do feel bad for my friends who didn't, but I was seeing Radiohead and they were too...so I don't feel that bad.]]></comment>
<comment author="Bwallen" timestamp="5:47 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 13, 2008"><![CDATA[It was cold and rainy, but hell it was a fantastic show.  Thom's jokes were hilarious and the setlist was great, hell, even the opening band was pretty good.  The only song they were missing was Creep, other than that, it was a fantastic show and will come out in any weather to see them again.]]></comment>
<comment author="WeirdFish" timestamp="3:43 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 13, 2008"><![CDATA[this was the most amazing concert of my life. Thom's voice was impeccable and the beauty of the songs brightened moods of all the soaken fans. The set list couldn't have been more perfect.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="Tyler" timestamp="2:57 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Freaking amazing.

Thom's opening line of "Hello, wet people!" was awesome.

The "rain down" section of Paranoid Android was the highlight of the night.

Totally worth freezing my ass off all night.]]></comment>
<comment author="optimistic" timestamp="9:19 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 13, 2008"><![CDATA[I was at the lawn for the whole show in the downpour and it was worth every second of it!
amazing performance and the light show is the best I've seen]]></comment>
<comment author="MCopp" timestamp="10:27 PM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[The weather was horrible, I was soaking wet and freezing, but none of that mattered because this was the most unbelievable show I have ever witnessed. The set was everything you could hope for and then more, without exaggeration. They put in a bit of an extra effort for the poor souls on the lawn. Once again they proved why they are the best band in music.]]></comment>
<comment author="Todd Wickersty" timestamp="7:51 PM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[My first Radiohead show (long time comin') and it was one of the best shows ever. I posted a review along with some photos and videos of Weird Fishes and Karma Police on my blog at http://thebutterroom.com/post/34607121]]></comment>
<comment author="Henry Shea" timestamp="5:36 PM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[It was raining harder than it did at Woodstock, the pit was way overcrowded and it was the best concert I have ever been to. Their set list was incredible, though, I wished that they had ended with Videotape, instead of playing it in the middle of the concert. The band was funny between songs and spot on the moment they started. ]]></comment>
<comment author="akshin14" timestamp="1:26 PM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[What an epic freaking show!!!  Sorry to all those that got flooded and couldn't make it.]]></comment>
<comment author="John" timestamp="12:24 PM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Thanks to all who braved the horrible rains and came to the show. That was one of the coolest audiences I've ever been a part of! What a great show.]]></comment>
<comment author="Jones" timestamp="11:02 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Outstanding performance! Let it rain! Luckily I had a seat but I feel the band put in an extra effort for the poor saps out on the lawn. I thought they would never top their setlist from the Camden, NJ show in August '03 but they did. Paranoid Android and Just back to back was a highlight. The lights and the screen in the back were awesome. Similar techniques to tours past but much improved. The new stuff, particularly 15 Step is great live. They rock everything out. Go see this tour!]]></comment>
<comment author="Sam Pulda" timestamp="8:54 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[What a nightmare of a venue. Radiohead was amazing, but with all the rain and apparent flooding, a 45-minute drive from DC took 3 hours down and 4 hours back. I will never go back, and encourage all others to do the same. Even a Radiohead show there in the future won't lure me back to Nissan. Hell the f'ing BEATLES could miraculously re-emerge and I won't go...]]></comment>
<comment author="cb" timestamp="7:49 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Long-time fan but my first show.  Everything - the band, sound, production, etc. - was amazing.  Great mix of old and new songs.  Very surprised to see so many songs from the Bends and OK Computer.  Encores had a great deal of energy, particularly National Anthem.  Thom dedicated Fake Plastic Trees to those who couldn't make it to the show because of flooding in the area delaying traffic (I missed the first six songs).  He also made a couple negative references to Capitol Hill, but I think it was a continuation of something he said before I arrived, so I didn't know what he was talking about.  Towards the end the band had a couple huddle-ups which made it seem like they were changing the setlist on the fly - very cool considering they brought out several of the classics.

I, along with many others, vow to never return to the venue because traffic is notoriously terrible, but it was well worth the seven hours to get there and back to DC and standing in the freezing rain.]]></comment>
<comment author="andrew" timestamp="7:40 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[I had two pit tickets and could not go due to the rain and the closed roads. Im so fucking pissed.I was in the car for 5 hours]]></comment>
<comment author="A. Petrick" timestamp="7:34 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Rain, rain, and more rain!  Although, I didn't let the constant downpour and 30 mph winds ruin a fantastic show.  The group is really coming close to perfecting the live show.  The lights for this '08 tour are amazing.  The colors during National Anthem were awesome!  Personal favs were Paranoid, P.T., and Ideoteque.  The only flaws were the mess-ups/restarts in Faust Arp and the short length of EIIRP (I've never seen one shorter).    All in all, great show...please, do they ever disappoint???        ]]></comment>
<comment author="Phil" timestamp="7:29 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Road flooded out, preventing us from getting to the show before the first encore.  Some never made it in.  Please Radiohead: Never play at the Nissan Pavilion again.  I certainly am never going back there.]]></comment>
<comment author="Rob" timestamp="5:15 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Nissan Pavilion sucks.  Spent 3 1/2 hours in traffic traveling 13 miles to get to the front gate.  I hope Radiohead and other bands stop playing there.]]></comment>
<comment author="jervin" timestamp="4:08 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Left DC with plenty of time to make the show.  Because of flood warning we were stuck in traffic for 4 hours (after we took the nissan pavillion exit) and ended up missing the entire show.  Very disapointing.  Looks like there were thousands upon thousands of people who were in the same situation.    ]]></comment>
<comment author="Dosed" timestamp="12:09 AM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[I know because my hands still hurt from clapping so hard..]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=624]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
