<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="26"><![CDATA[Massachusetts]]></locale>
<city id="155"><![CDATA[Mansfield]]></city>
<venue id="257"><![CDATA[Tweeter Center]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Tweeter+Center</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Wednesday, August 13, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>656</previousshow>
<nextshow>658</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Grizzly Bear]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="2" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="3" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="4" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="5" id="39"><![CDATA[Kid A]]></track>
<track num="6" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="7" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="8" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="9" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="10" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="11" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="12" id="17"><![CDATA[The Bends]]></track>
<track num="13" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="14" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="15" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="16" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="19" id="52"><![CDATA[I Might Be Wrong]]></track>
<track num="20" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="21" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="22" id="41"><![CDATA[How To Disappear Completely]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="155"><![CDATA[Cymbal Rush]]></track>
<track num="24" id="2"><![CDATA[Karma Police]]></track>
<track num="25" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[klutch.xls]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[CocoacabanaBoy]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jrob]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[drtchocky]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dreamsie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fradleybox]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[robotchant]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pzykotic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Z92]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Herrminator]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[FriedNaiveFog]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pure]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[trojanpony]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[browncrayon]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[inarcadia]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[benrosol]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[deathisadoorway5]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Metabolic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[agloriousday]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[redsox2kx2]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jzkpr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Pete2186]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[baildon]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[beaucolburn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[niteshft]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[citizenlowell]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tbullard16]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ptang945]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[magomra]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[spacepanda]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cmoran9]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jimcnet]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[terry4322]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Idaa]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[michaelmirra]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[midoherty]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[Update #1 (17:20 PDT):  Our setlist correspondent has checked in from the venue, so all systems are go.  Grizzly Bear has just taken the stage in Mansfield.  Let the show begin!<br><br>PS: In case you were around for last night's debacle, tonight should be better.  We're using a correspondent that's successfully helped us on a prior setlist broadcast.<br><br>cheers!<br>b.
<br><br><br>
Update #2 (17:46 PDT): Grizzly bear has just finished.  Radiohead should be on roundabouts 18:00 PDT.
<br><br><br>
Update #3 (18:28 PDT): We're rolling super-smooth, updating the setlist tonight thanks to both of our texters!]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="milos57" timestamp="1:11 AM [PST], Tuesday, September 23, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my first Radiohead show, and it was an emotionally moving and overall mind-blowing experience. They put incredible love and energy into each song, the list of which was nicely filled out, with some surprises. Videotape, Weird Fishes, and 15 Step were fantastic, as were Idioteque, The National Anthem, Exit Music, Cymbal Rush, and I Might Be Wrong (nice surprise there). For me, the highlight of the night was How To Disappear Completely. The string outro that was played for whole minutes after the song ended was one of the most eerie pieces of music I've ever heard live. 

I would've loved Fake Plastic Trees, My Iron Lung, or Street Spirit somewhere in the mix, but then again, you need something to root for next time you see a band like Radiohead in concert. ]]></comment>
<comment author="a weird fish" timestamp="2:31 PM [PST], Monday, August 18, 2008"><![CDATA[Yeah! they totally started out with "Dr Baker" by the Betas.  I love that song, I love that band, wish they hadn't broken up...
Regardless, this show was flippin' mind blowing.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="Soup" timestamp="6:32 PM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[Did anyone here pick up on the intro to Everything in its Right Place?  I think it was Dr. Baker by the Beta Band, which is interesting because they opened for Radiohead 7 or so years ago when I saw them play Wonderland.]]></comment>
<comment author="talkingtoomuch" timestamp="4:11 PM [PST], Saturday, August 16, 2008"><![CDATA[i was completely blown away by this performance. The  trippy futuristic sounds right before they walked on stage got everyone hyped and ready to see them. I'm surprised no one has said anything about that yet I thought that was a nice small touch. Reckoner was a great opener, the light show was amazing. Every song from In Rainbows was played, house of cards was amazing. Their sound was just perfect. I will definitely see them again without a question.]]></comment>
<comment author="BDub" timestamp="4:28 PM [PST], Friday, August 15, 2008"><![CDATA[To the six (three guys/three gals) inconsiderate hippies strung out on X, with your red day glo wrist bands, constant smoking, dancing and throwing yourself into other people with no regard for ANYONE around you...even you could not ruin my first (and transcendent!) show with Radiohead.  You kept telling me and my friends to mellow out...well, in my late 30s, I was there for the music, not the drugs...so if you read this, if you need mind altering chems to heighten the show for you, you're not the fans you claimed to be!  Enough negativity, down off my soapbox!  Sound and lights were the best I've seen, and this first timer was blown away by selections from Kid A, and Idioteque remains surreal!!!  Can't wait for number two!  Peace, and remember your neighbors next time you're at a show!!!!  Be considerate!]]></comment>
<comment author="TomD" timestamp="12:28 PM [PST], Friday, August 15, 2008"><![CDATA[I agree with that.  The songs from Kid A sounded absolutely amazing.  And while Jigsaw is my favorite of In Rainbows, I was a little disappointed  with how it sounded.  O well, not complaining.  So many other moments completely knocked me on my ass.  Wolf at the door?  holy wow, that was amazing.]]></comment>
<comment author="whoskennybunker?" timestamp="11:08 AM [PST], Friday, August 15, 2008"><![CDATA[Was my first time seeing Radiohead live and i definitely was not disappointed --well maybe a little bit. The band was great and the songs were performed awesome. I just wish they had played more songs off of OK Computer (namely Let Down or Lucky), but three were enough. The only gripe I have is that I didn't buy better seats. Being on the lawn and having to stand the whole time puts a toll on your back, and then during Exit Music some annoying drunk chick keep screaming right next to my ear (watcha gonna do?). Anyways it was a great performance, light show was amazing.]]></comment>
<comment author="Sam" timestamp="6:59 AM [PST], Friday, August 15, 2008"><![CDATA[It was interesting to see how each album sounded live. I was amazed by how great KID A sounded, Idoteque was incredable live. Paranoid Android aswell sounded incredible acompanied by the Blurry rainbow lights. I was disapointed to hear jigsaw and bodysnatchers a little less crisp than the older tracks, I guess they get better with time?]]></comment>
<comment author="Semmy" timestamp="3:56 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[thank you for mentioning I Migt Be Wrong, what the hell, i would've loved to see it too. SOMEBODY put some damn videos up already!]]></comment>
<comment author="scott" timestamp="3:46 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[absolutely blown away! third time seeing them and it was the best yet. setlist was fantastic and thom even did cymbal rush which was sweet. how to disappear comepletely was a special treat for me since i never heard it live(missed kid a tour). the lights and thom's red skinny jeans rocked.]]></comment>
<comment author="English Mike" timestamp="3:32 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[Someone asked for the set list and which CDs they came off,  so I W.A.S.T.E.d a could of hours to give to that. No crowd sucks, they got off their @$${$ and went didn't they .. Nice singing on Karma Police - beauiful!
Radiohead Concert
Venue: Comcast Center. Mansfield, MA
Start Time: August 13th, 2008 8:45pm	End Time: August 13th, 2008 10:53pm  
Play List
	Starting Set
1.	Reckoner  - From In Rainbows  Track 7
2.	Optimistic   From Kid A  Track 6
3.	There There (The Boney King of Nowhere)  From Hail to the Thief  Track 9
4.	15 Step  From In Rainbows  Track 1
5.	Kid A  From Kid A  Track 2
6.	Nude  From In Rainbows  Track 3
7.	All I Need  From In Rainbows  Track 5
8.	The Gloaming (Softly Open Our Mouths in the Cold)  From Hail to the Thief  Track 8
9.	The National Anthem  From Kid A  Track 3
10.	Videotape  From In Rainbows  Track 10
11.	Jigsaw Falling Into Place  From In Rainbows  Track 9
12.	The Bends  From The Bends  Track 7
13.	Faust Arp  From In Rainbows  Track 6
14.	Weird Fishes/Arpeggi  From In Rainbows  Track 4
15.	Everything in its Right Place  From Kid A  Track 1
16.	Exit Music (for a Film)  From OK Computer  Track 2
17.	Bodysnatchers  From In Rainbows  Track 2

First Encore
18.	House of Cards  From In Rainbows  Track 8
19.	I Might Be Wrong  From Amnesiac  Track 5
20.	Paranoid Android  From OK Computer  Track 2
21.	Wolf at the Door (It Girl. Rag Doll)  From Hail to the Thief  Track 14
22.	How to Disappear Completely  From Kid A  Track 4

Second Encore
23.	Cymbal Rush  From The Eraser  Track 9
24.	Karma Police  From OK Computer  Track 6
25.	Idioteque  From Kid A  Track 8

Enjoy!]]></comment>
<comment author="mark" timestamp="2:44 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[i'm surprised no one has mentioned the gloaming as a highlight.  i was more pleasantly surprised at the kid a material than anything else--it packed more of a punch than it does on record.  and of course exit music was absolutely breathtaking.  i especially enjoyed watching jonny the mad scientist work his magic...i could go on and on.  the entire experience added up to the best show i've seen in years--thanks, guys.]]></comment>
<comment author="sean" timestamp="1:59 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[This is the 3rd RH live show for me (the others in LA at smaller/better venues), and it is unquestionably the very best live show of RH's or anyone else I've witnessed to this day. I was transported. That venue has horrific acoustics and the crowd was a bit sluggish/thuggish, but screw it man, what a dream the experience was!]]></comment>
<comment author="shaun" timestamp="12:39 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[Not a word from you guys about the first I might be Wrong of the tour. I would have killed to hear this a few weeks ago at Deer Creek.]]></comment>
<comment author="bob Bunker" timestamp="12:15 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[absolutely blown away.  first time seeing the boys, and man did they deliver.  I loved the set list the light show was unreal and thom's dancing was top-notch.  Been waiting a real long time to see them and man was it worth the wait]]></comment>
<comment author="chris" timestamp="11:27 AM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[First Radiohead show, and it was amazing. They were tight and played flawlessly.  And yes, to agree with the reviewer below, the sound at Greatwoods (it will always be Greatwoods to me) was extraordinary.  I will say that while I certainly didn't mind hearing the new album in it's entirety, I can agree with some that the older material could have been a little more spread out. I love Kid A as much as the next person, but only one song from the bends and 3 from Ok Computer?  With 6 from Kid A?? It took me a long time to see these guys and I loved every minute of the show, I just would have liked to have heard a few more from those albums. But hey, there could be a next time :-)]]></comment>
<comment author="spiral" timestamp="10:53 AM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[I don't see how people can complain about choice of songs when the band switches it up every nite. If you really want to be covered you have to commit to a week of traveling to different venues, which is the most fun way to do shows anyway. You know, get a different perspective. The show last nite was outstanding. I have been to many many concerts in my life (about 700) and this was up there with the best of em. 

PS: playing lots of material from an album that you are touring to support, not un common. What is uncommon is for a band to be smart enough to switch the other material upso that it all stays interesting to them every nite. If its interesting for them, that relays to the audience]]></comment>
<comment author="lissa" timestamp="10:35 AM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[beautiful show. the lights were incredible! liked reckoner as the opener, wolf at the door was nuts (!), exit music was fantastic. cymbal rush was cool just because the entire stadium was silent...very intense. 

paying bank for the pit was well worth it, just to watch ed make faces and thom flail up close.

fingers crossed for 2+2 and fake plastic in san fran...]]></comment>
<comment author="David" timestamp="10:26 AM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[it was honestly the amazing show ever but the only nag i can point out was that they didn't play airbag or 2 + 2 = 5. oh and +50 for thom's red pants + funky dancin']]></comment>
<comment author="Jeff" timestamp="9:52 AM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[I would have taken 2+2=5 over Karma Police in a heartbeat.

It was on my short-list of songs I wanted them to play. :)]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=657]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
