<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="12"><![CDATA[Texas]]></locale>
<city id="15"><![CDATA[Woodlands]]></city>
<venue id="4"><![CDATA[C.W. Mitchell Pavillion]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>C.W.+Mitchell+Pavillion</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Wednesday, October 01, 2003</showdate>
<tour id="9"><![CDATA[Hail To The Thief]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>392</previousshow>
<nextshow>394</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Supergrass]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="75"><![CDATA[2&#43;2=5]]></track>
<track num="2" id="93"><![CDATA[Sit Down. Stand Up.]]></track>
<track num="3" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="4" id="138"><![CDATA[Backdrifts]]></track>
<track num="5" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="6" id="14"><![CDATA[Lurgee]]></track>
<track num="7" id="88"><![CDATA[Scatterbrain]]></track>
<track num="8" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="9" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="10" id="60"><![CDATA[Sail To The Moon]]></track>
<track num="11" id="94"><![CDATA[Go To Sleep]]></track>
<track num="12" id="52"><![CDATA[I Might Be Wrong]]></track>
<track num="13" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="14" id="54"><![CDATA[Dollars & Cents]]></track>
<track num="15" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="16" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="17" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="19" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="20" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="21" id="19"><![CDATA[Fake Plastic Trees]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="22" id="2"><![CDATA[Karma Police]]></track>
<track num="23" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[empeaks]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[caravanpikey]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bptx]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mwing]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[1inamill1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[5dayweekend]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cmilazzo]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardlylurkin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rhfans]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[zavalito]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="Garo" timestamp="11:27 PM [PST], Saturday, May 01, 2004"><![CDATA[hi, im from mexico and i just want to say that this performance was very special to me and i never seen something like it not even close, the setlist was awsome, even more than others performed in Europe, these are 5 exellent muscicians communicating in perfect harmony to create not only a unique musical experience but to provide the audience a breathtaking stage performance, ligths perfectly coordinated with music..jonny what can i say, incredible guitar solo(dodecaphonic like)...anyway i sorted a lot of obstacles to get there..it worth it.]]></comment>
<comment author="Bonnie" timestamp="11:15 PM [PST], Tuesday, October 07, 2003"><![CDATA[That was my first Radiohead show and I loved it. I loved Thom's facial expressions and especially his dancing. You could tell he really feels his music. Hats off to the lead guitartist for putting on a great show. I loved the show and hope to see more in the future. Even though Creep is played out I would love to see them sing it live one day. And I would love to hear Talk Show Host. ]]></comment>
<comment author="Brian" timestamp="2:41 PM [PST], Tuesday, October 07, 2003"><![CDATA[They came from the musical gods and reigned on us for a good 2 hours. 2 hours that changed many lives for sure. how does greenwood do it? on backdrifts and just? how can a human play that fast and not break a string or make one mistake? how can thom's voice mimic an angel here on earth with sail to the moon and fake plastic trees? anyone who thinks they dont rock after a wolf at the door need not ever listen to radiohead again with a good conscious. in conclusion...best show ever!]]></comment>
<comment author="Philip" timestamp="2:20 PM [PST], Monday, October 06, 2003"><![CDATA[This show was my first Radiohead show, and hopefully not my last. I have never heard three guitars sound better together live. Lurgee was my highlight, and of course everything off of the new album was brilliant. I was praying for Bulletproof and my buddies all wanted True love waits, but you could not have left that show unhappy.]]></comment>
<comment author="Guga" timestamp="11:10 AM [PST], Friday, October 03, 2003"><![CDATA[To cath The Band on this tour is a pure luck,like catching Pink Floyd Tour in 1972.-they re blowing everybodys brains out on every show,crowds are enjoying and the band is really on their prime.You can think this and that about past 3 albums-this is too left,that is too far-but everythings gets clear once you see this all packaged live.Mighty and superb.Gives you optimism that there is still some new ways out here,that we wontbe all drown in a sea of plastic clons.
Im fourty years old dynosaurus,but i never saw better show.Period.
Yes,and nice play for Supergrass.Well hear more of them.]]></comment>
<comment author="Will" timestamp="5:58 AM [PST], Friday, October 03, 2003"><![CDATA[Good concert, but not the best one that I've ever seen them at.  They didn't play a bunch of the songs that I was hoping for (i.e. Exit Music, Iron Lung, Myxomatosis, Talk Show Host, etc.).  There were a couple tracks off the new album that they played that I wished were replaced with others.  Still, the highlights of the show were There There (obviously), Just, National Anthem, and Wolf at the Door.  I'd give it a B+...although the other two times I have seen them were A+'s.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=393]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
