<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="1"><![CDATA[California]]></locale>
<city id="186"><![CDATA[Indio]]></city>
<venue id="319"><![CDATA[Empire Polo Fields]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Empire+Polo+Fields</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Saturday, May 01, 2004</showdate>
<tour id="9"><![CDATA[Hail To The Thief]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>435</previousshow>
<nextshow>579</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="2" id="75"><![CDATA[2&#43;2=5]]></track>
<track num="3" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="4" id="89"><![CDATA[Myxomatosis]]></track>
<track num="5" id="23"><![CDATA[My Iron Lung]]></track>
<track num="6" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="7" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="8" id="2"><![CDATA[Karma Police]]></track>
<track num="9" id="60"><![CDATA[Sail To The Moon]]></track>
<track num="10" id="52"><![CDATA[I Might Be Wrong]]></track>
<track num="11" id="93"><![CDATA[Sit Down. Stand Up.]]></track>
<track num="12" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="13" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="14" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="15" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="16" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="17" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="18" id="16"><![CDATA[Planet Telex]]></track>
<track num="19" id="6"><![CDATA[Creep]]></track>
<track num="20" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore1>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[brian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tenacious z]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[peterpan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[polyethylene]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[black_star42]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Vancouver]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[duder]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[yuki]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[microcuts]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[industry71]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[superjen83]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[yalzin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[polystyrened]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Mad Clown]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jsandler]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[klutch.xls]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tubro]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fakeplastic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[darkalian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[zaydon]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[debaser]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lex]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lost-child]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardhead]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[toad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dreamsie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fradleybox]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[zara.]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jas282]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[madaski29]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[collapsed]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pizzmoe]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Tabooty]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jenniferrae]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[knphilli]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Bort]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Shoestars]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pworks]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[randyrad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[plainclothes_man]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blueplaydoh]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neekole]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[wierdfishee]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lsylv]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[timedilute]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[taurina]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[agentonze]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jdsaciv]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Battering Room]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jreedmiller]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chules]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[godthizza]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dymo23]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[daviddi33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[leifdog222]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Arianna]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pion]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bigdaddy]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thefullearth]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fakeplasticme]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[scatterbrain83]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dubstar]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[nickdavey]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Pete2186]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[edotdotdot]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[MattHeckman]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dapp]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sauce]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[entheogen111]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mahntoh]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[stefanglidden]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[piz]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cygnus7]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[devgum]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[CaptainFloyd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<uplink>
<check>
<link num="1" time="4:32 PM (PST)" user="brian" status="OK"></link>
<check>
<link num="2" time="8:24 PM (PST)" user="brian" status="OK"></link>
</check>
<images>
<image member="brian" src="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/000003_tb.jpg" link="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/000003.jpg" title="Thom going crazy. "/>
<image member="brian" src="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/000001_tb.jpg" link="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/000001.jpg" title="The sun comes down on Coachella. "/>
<image member="brian" src="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/000002_tb.jpg" link="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/000002.jpg" title="And the lights rise before the encore... "/>
</images>
<comments>
<comment author="graham " timestamp="5:13 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 18, 2004"><![CDATA[i drove 30 hrs straight for the concert and it was worth every minute of the terrible heat and boredom on the way. But radiohead once again blew me away.  They are the greatest live show on the planet and that alone made it worth it.  Not to mention the pixies, flaming lips, muse etc. ]]></comment>
<comment author="omar" timestamp="12:17 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 12, 2004"><![CDATA[i drove 10 hours from Mexico just to see the Pixies and Radiohead... they both rocked coachella!!! Coachella was soo kewl.  I only hoped you stayed sunday for Belle & Sebastian, Air and Flaming Lips... it was all good!!

Hope to be there next year! cant wait. ]]></comment>
<comment author="rob" timestamp="7:45 PM [PST], Monday, May 10, 2004"><![CDATA["i've seen them over 10 times through the years and this was really not a very good show. Anyone who claims it was incredible hasn't seen them at their best." 

very arrogant... nonetheless, it was a great show and finale to their httt tour.]]></comment>
<comment author="Matt" timestamp="6:29 PM [PST], Sunday, May 09, 2004"><![CDATA[I can't describe how great this weekend was.  This was the strongest set I've ever seen them play.  Planet Telex!  Jonny programmed new sounds for idioteque, myxomatosis was amazing/different.  Thom had more energy than usual.  As much as I didn't really like creep I love it now, awesome - light show.  I wet myself.  I wish they would throw in more rarities, but well worth the trip.  You can go here to download the show.  You have to save as .mp3. http://www.okcomputer-fr.net/index02.html]]></comment>
<comment author="Nicole" timestamp="12:21 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 05, 2004"><![CDATA[What a special performance! I never thought I would here Radiohead perform Creep -that was special! Looking for a recording--anyone out there w/ access to a bootleg! PLease contact me! I have gotten them in th past! Thank you Radiohead for a beautiful performance!!]]></comment>
<comment author="jsteele" timestamp="12:21 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 05, 2004"><![CDATA[After There There and the build up of 2+2=5 the crowd was nuts. The sun sets, they start in on lucky and the 50,000 sun-stroked delerious screaming fans were spellbound and silenced - it was a unique experience. This is what we have instead of religion? It was the best version of I Might Be Wrong i've heard in person or bootleged. They played National Anthem, Paranoid Andriod then Idioteque; as my brother said, "i think thats when i shit my pants." 

Greatness is blatant, it's obvious. Radiohead was oozing it from every pore and frankly put every other performance at Coachella into its place. I'd keep babbling but you either know what i'm talking about or haven't seen them live yet. Their studio albums are fantastic but the live performances are on a whole different leve. If a copy of this show is circling let me know @ jsteele546@hotmail.com. I'll send you a kidney or something, whatever you want.]]></comment>
<comment author="jonathan" timestamp="12:11 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 05, 2004"><![CDATA[being as close as i was to the band was spiritual. people dancing, jumping up and down, and getting into trance like states (the gloaming) was so fun to be a part of. there were times when thom sounded very weird, almost an evil version of himself (i think it was the infection) but nevertheless, i can honestly say i've never been so blown away in my life.]]></comment>
<comment author="Johnny" timestamp="11:15 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[The message is clear, we are listening and waiting for more.  Now that someone has woken us up, we are empowered by this music to stay awake.  The Coachella show was amazing, the energy released was abnormal, exactly like the band, thank you for hope.]]></comment>
<comment author="Rebecca" timestamp="7:00 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[I have been to a lot of shows, and I have even seen Radiohead before (with another favorite of mine, Stephen Malkmus, opening last August) but the Coachella performance was definitely the most powerful and moving performance I have ever seen in my entire life. They were dead on, they played so many great songs, and their stage presence was amazing. Ach! I LOVE RADIOHEAD!]]></comment>
<comment author="eddieG." timestamp="6:11 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[The most important band at the moment.I was in about the 3rd row in the pit and shouted to Collin and he pointed at me!Jonny actually moved to Ed's side from time to time and there were moments where he would just hug the guitar.This is the best dam show i've ever seen.....and i saw Phantom Planet right after. the day was hottttttt.]]></comment>
<comment author="mediaassassin" timestamp="4:14 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[After the rumors that the band might have to pull out of the festival, any Radiohead show would have been fantastic.  This one lived up to expectations, and if I hadn't known Thom had been ill beforehand, I don't think I would have noticed it.  I could tell he wasn't performing his best, but only because I was looking for flaws.  All in all, an excellent show.  This was my sixth Radiohead show, and the closest I've been to the stage since I was in the front row at the Hollywood Bowl a few years back.  We did get to hear a few tracks I don't think I heard the other times I saw them on this tour, including Planet Telex, My Iron Lung and Karma Police, which were all aweseome to see.  Can't wait to hear the new EP!!]]></comment>
<comment author="brandi" timestamp="3:28 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[this show was just plain BEAUTIFUL! this was my first time seeing radiohead, and i was utterly blown away. i managed to record all of myxomatosis (thom's crazy dancing was utterly breathtaking,) and parts of creep, no surprises (my favorite!) karma police, and lucky.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="Molly Nee" timestamp="3:14 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[i've seen them over 10 times through the years and this was really not a very good show. Anyone who claims it was incredible hasn't seen them at their best. This was an ok performance, at best. Thom's voice was weak and the band seemed tired. Still,  always good to see the boys. ]]></comment>
<comment author="amy crescenzo" timestamp="12:14 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[A fantastic mix of songs! Altough I love the new album, they played almost as many from OK Computer, with a delightful smattering off of the others. Does anyone know if anyone recorded any of it? Perhaps all of it? Maybe off of the soundboard? Please? ]]></comment>
<comment author="Alejandro Arce" timestamp="8:26 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[If you ever have an opportunity to see Radiohead, DO IT! or you'll miss true greatness in music performed live. After the drowning in heat, I came to a most joyous bliss. "Only he who has experienced, understands what I mean".]]></comment>
<comment author="Adam" timestamp="1:47 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[I saw Radiohead at the Hollywood Bowl in October.  I was so far away and such that I just couldn't get into it.  At the time I also was not a huge fan of anything from Kid A on.  However, the show completely turned me around and really opened my eyes.  Naturally I wanted to be able to see them again so I could really take it all in.  This performance point me in an entirely different world.  It stands up to the best performances I've ever seen from Tool, Rage, Beck, ATDI, Primus, RHCP, and many other bands whose music has influenced me and whose performances transformed me.  This is a show that truly took me to another place.  I can't imagine not having made the sacrifice of sleep and comfort for this incredible show.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="_t" timestamp="12:05 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[I've seen RH 4 times now and I must say from the moment they stepped onstage, they completely killed.  Total bloodbath.  Not a downpoint in the set, twas evident that they put their all into each and every song.  Dug the funked out version of I Might Be Wrong.  New life was added everywhere... I can't say how much longer Planet Telex & My Iron Lung were from the album versions.

bootleg anyone?]]></comment>
<comment author="Mr. Alexander Z" timestamp="12:04 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[Well, it's only fair to say that this was... you cant really say what it was!!!! It was just fucking awesome, so awesome that an explicit bad word can't even display the excitement and purity this event had on a distorted soul--like myself. 

A little addition to the list though, they began with Paperbag Writer (Com Lag), but they only played the first few seconds. It threw almost all extreme Radiohead fans into a frenzy of confusion when There There (Hail to the Thief) began to play with two giant drums on both sides of the stage. 

Un-fucking-believable!

~Z]]></comment>
<comment author="Lonewolf" timestamp="11:25 PM [PST], Monday, May 03, 2004"><![CDATA[[The Beginning]

This was my first time at Coachella, and even though I consider myself a fan, it was also the first time I've ever seen Radiohead play live (I live in Phoenix which maybe one reason why). With so many first time experiences, I'm prompted to write a full review. Here we go.

[There There]

I wasn't very happy with the venue and by the time Radiohead came on I felt I was within an inch of dying from dehydration. It's really a testament to the band that I stayed to watch them and even more so that their performance was so good I actually felt like the money I spent attending was worth it. That's how good the band's performance was. Let us break it down.

[I could be wrong]

The wait for Radiohead seemed to take hours (it was more like forty minutes) as the Pixies left the stage, more and more advanced lighting equipment was being hauled on stage. If anything I knew the band was going to have excellent lighting (which they did), but when you're waiting in the desert heat, forty minutes can seem like a lifetime. When the band did take the stage the light show that ensued was top notch. There was twinkle lights in the background, some seizure inducing strobe lights to the left and right and the usual nice slanted Coachella stage lighting plus fog machines, the works. During certain songs, the stage would be enveloped in a certain color, each seeming to match the song they were playing. There were two LCD screens, one on each side of the stage. The band opened with There There at which point the right screen was split showing an image of Thom on top and Johnny on the bottom and the screen to the left was likewise split showing everything else (you can tell what screen I was looking at). There There was nice and filled me with excitement as well as anticipation, 2+2=5 was next and I began to worry that all of the songs would be off Hail to the Thief (this being my first live Radiohead show) little did I know, I was in for the full treatment. When 2+2 reach its climax, the audience climaxed as well. Everyone was going crazy and then they brought it down a notch with Lucky. I was surprised that they played Lucky and was hopeful that more OK Computer songs maybe played. The bands performance of Lucky was truly beautiful and then Kool Keith took the live stage to the right and his set could be heard drowning out Lucky and ruining one of the more poignant moments of the song. This prompted some fans to shout TURN THAT SHIT OFF!!! Radiohead responded by turning the amp up and blasting Myxomatosis climaxing with Thom break dancing to the screams of the crowd. I could still hear loud scratching coming from Kool Keith's set and blending in nicely with Myxomatosis. It was kind of weird.

[sit down, stand up]

Thom erupted into his trademark epileptic dance and was very playful with the audience. There were three full blown sing-a-longs: Karma Police, Paranoid Android and of course Creep. There were many half sing-a-longs including Lucky, Exit Music and Street Spirit. Thom played with the audience during You And Whose Army by looking at the camera evilly and gesturing at the audience inciting them by asking "You and whose army...you should have known better!!!" (or something like that). 

[End]

The crowd at Coachella must have been fairly hardcore as fans because the crowd (me included) did quite alot of singing and jumping up and down and most people knew all of the words to most of the songs. There were roars of approval for almost everything Thom and company did. He ended the concert by thanking the Pixies and saying that the Pixies and REM changed his life. This sent up more roars of approval from the audience. All and all it was a nice first time experience, but, I hope I get a chance to see Radiohead at a more proper venue next time.
]]></comment>
<comment author="fingerdown" timestamp="10:22 PM [PST], Monday, May 03, 2004"><![CDATA[A more mellow performance than the show I saw in September '03 at the Shorline Amphitheater, but spectacular nonetheless.  
Their entire production is as close to perfection as possible:  sound, lighting, atmosphere and performance. 
Undoubtedly the most important band in music currently.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=434]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
