<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="24"><![CDATA[Ohio]]></locale>
<city id="10"><![CDATA[Cuyahoga Falls]]></city>
<venue id="98"><![CDATA[Blossom Music Center]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Blossom+Music+Center</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Monday, August 04, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>635</previousshow>
<nextshow>637</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="3" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="4" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="5" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="6" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="7" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="8" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="9" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="10" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="11" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="12" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="13" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="14" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="15" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="16" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
<track num="17" id="41"><![CDATA[How To Disappear Completely]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="19" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="20" id="54"><![CDATA[Dollars & Cents]]></track>
<track num="21" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="22" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="24" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="25" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardhead]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[DentonFreeman]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[RKShew]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ruddtherudd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ImaCreep]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[harvey]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bebeto21]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[doc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blue_trane]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jig1781]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[RockKing]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[emagdnim015]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[topsyturvytown]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chuck1003]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[masuther]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[babysgotthebends]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Idaa]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jfiveeight]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="heddie" timestamp="11:17 PM [PST], Saturday, August 09, 2008"><![CDATA[i've seen them 4 times and this was the best setlist and best in general...street spirit ah could anyone ask for more...wolf at the door was great too well everything was great but this was by far the best night of my life such an amazing band and such talent i can't say anymore except i need to see them again]]></comment>
<comment author="ChrisC." timestamp="6:07 PM [PST], Friday, August 08, 2008"><![CDATA[I've seen many concerts over the years, but Radiohead has to be one of the best. Unparalleled combination of musicianship/lighting-staging out there today. Absolutely no complaints w/ the set list (everyone has their favorite songs, but I understand that not every song can be played. And we all know that In Rainbows HAS to be well represented). I was very excited that they played Wolf At The Door and Climbing Up The Wall. The Gloaming and Dollars And Cents have now become new favorites of mine. I'll treasure this concert and keep the memories of this night forever. Thank you Radiohead, come back to Cleveland soon.]]></comment>
<comment author="DJPutzo" timestamp="6:06 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 06, 2008"><![CDATA[I've been a fan since pablo honey, and finally got to see them live. I was absolutely blown away!! The setlist was just perfect, the light show rocked, and the venue and crowd was a real treat. you can bet i will see them again! Oh yeah.....PYRAMID SONG!!!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="Mike" timestamp="8:54 PM [PST], Tuesday, August 05, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my 2nd time seeing Radiohead, last time was in 2003 when they last came through Cleveland. This show put the last one to shame. A few thoughts:
Great, great setlist...lighting was amazing....Thom and Jonny playing Faust Arp acoustic was beautiful...Glad we got Street Spirit (Fade Out), but would have loved more from The Bends....National Anthem was transcendent...lighting was amazing....The Gloaming and Climbing Up The Walls were two songs that are SOOO much better live (and Im even a fan of those songs to begin with)....Paranoid Android is still one of the top 5 greatest songs ever written....light show was AMAZING....the band really seemed to be enjoying themselves....THE LIGHT SHOW WAS AMAZING
I've seen over 100 bands. From Paul McCartney to Primus, from Dave Matthews to The Who, from Digital Underground to Bela Fleck and the Flecktones, from Roger Waters "Dark Side" tour to Beck front row at Cleveland's House of Blues.... This show is immediately ranked in my top 5 shows I have ever seen. I have some thinking to do before I rank it above McCartney and Waters (the 2 greatest concerts Ive been to), but this might bump Beck from the Top 3.
"Astounding" was my one word text review to a friend afterwards. It truly was.]]></comment>
<comment author="emay" timestamp="2:00 PM [PST], Tuesday, August 05, 2008"><![CDATA[Was it 9/ where TY screeched "I saw this all coming"?

"We had nothing better to do". Neither did we, band. Perhaps a poke, but thank you regardless.]]></comment>
<comment author="Dylan" timestamp="12:45 PM [PST], Tuesday, August 05, 2008"><![CDATA[Awesome show... first time seeing Radiohead live and I was completely blown away.  The light show was a feat by itself.]]></comment>
<comment author="RKShew" timestamp="12:00 PM [PST], Tuesday, August 05, 2008"><![CDATA[Fantastic venue, crowd.  Light show amazing, as per previous reports.  Sound was very clean, didn't need earplugs like in 2003 (either the sound is much better, or I'm going deaf).  Standout songs:
Morning Bell - after the song, Thom came to the front of stage and sang the rhythmic backgound vocals a capella for a good 30-45 seconds (a real treat)
The Gloaming - did not expect this song to rock, but it came quite aggressively, much to the enjoyment of all
National Anthem - blew the crowd away with the pressure they added to this with the light tube display flashing bright red and white at near strobe velocity!
Dollars & Cents - I'd forgotten about this gem on Amnesiac.  Live, they made it sound like the best song I've never heard, ever!
Everything In Its Right Place - fantastic, evolved into extended rhythmic coda, with each member leaving in turn. The guitars were left to their own freaking chords for a good minute or so after the last bandmates left the stage.  Finally, the roadies came out to turn 'em off.  Good night!
]]></comment>
<comment author="eric t" timestamp="9:11 AM [PST], Tuesday, August 05, 2008"><![CDATA[this was the greatest night of my life. The setlist they chose just blew me away. I would have been happy no matter which songs they plays bu I don't think I could have asked foe anythig better. The music sounded perfect. Thin looked like he was having a blast and he did the coolest dances ever. Amazing]]></comment>
<comment author="sbilas" timestamp="10:24 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[at the end i thought they were playing everything in it's right place, the stage had letters flashing spelling everything, then the band all walked off individually]]></comment>
<comment author="Kid A" timestamp="8:58 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[WOW!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="ruth" timestamp="7:52 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[24. Lucky (Thom, Thanks to Grizzly Bear. Hello Everyone.)
]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=636]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
