<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="1"><![CDATA[California]]></locale>
<city id="173"><![CDATA[Chula Vista]]></city>
<venue id="291"><![CDATA[Cricket Wireless Amphitheatre]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Cricket+Wireless+Amphitheatre</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Wednesday, August 27, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>663</previousshow>
<nextshow>665</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="3" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="4" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="5" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="6" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="7" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="8" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="9" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="10" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="11" id="41"><![CDATA[How To Disappear Completely]]></track>
<track num="12" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="13" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="14" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="15" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="16" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="19" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="20" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="21" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="22" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="24" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="25" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jessica]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dleach31]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[debaser]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Tabooty]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neekole]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lucky Schnauzer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ATLFalconsFAN]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lodi]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[prez2024]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[scatterbrain83]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[nickdavey]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[swimnmex]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sauce]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Kid Julian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[redsoxfaan3]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[caliboy256]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[will_i_am]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dennisdster]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[devgum]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[MothMessage]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chaos_lynn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[markcharlessmith]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[michaelmirra]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fugu-fish]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rbarthjr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rhfans]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="Switters." timestamp="2:12 PM [PST], Saturday, August 30, 2008"><![CDATA["Perfect" isn't the right word, but it's the first word that comes to mind. The show had a certain vibe about it, a particular vibe. That vibe is reigning over love and lust, somewhere right now. Radiohead was giving us presents and we open all them and gave them our own. The best two hours of my life. After those two hours, it all went to hell, but, memories of those hours will haunt my dreams, but not a bad haunting, but a Casper. Everyone should experience a Radiohead concert, at least once in there lives.
]]></comment>
<comment author="Lodi" timestamp="6:25 PM [PST], Friday, August 29, 2008"><![CDATA[Best damn 2nd show ever!

Got Ed's drumstick!!! Hell yeah.

The rail is where the fun is at.

And thanks to all the wonderful people I met during the line. You're all awesome.]]></comment>
<comment author="Sam" timestamp="8:47 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[GREAT SHOW!!! my first ever!!! from the pit wooo
it was so awesome. omg climbing up the walls anyone?

a-train i got some pretty good pics but i cant find my usb cord!
]]></comment>
<comment author="A-Train" timestamp="5:04 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[The comments below sum it up! This was my 4th Radiohead show and they rocked my sox beautifully.

Did anyone get a bootleg of this? I'm totally down for trading.

And did anyone get SWEET photos from the pit? I was in the pit, but I didnt bring a cam... DOH!]]></comment>
<comment author="Jimmy Bee" timestamp="1:39 PM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Don't know why people have to review a RH show by comparing it to the Bowl, it was nothing like those shows. The vibe and performances were INCREDIBLE. The energy the fans were feeding the band (especially in the pit) and vice versa, fueled one of the best concerts I have ever seen from them. Climbing Up The Walls was easily the best version of it I have ever heard, holy ****. Optimistic was bad*** too. How about Just, HTDC, Talk Show Host, YAWA?, Lucky and Street Spirit? They were all unbelievably earth-shatteringly incredible. Every person I met was extremely friendly and we all shared in the show's so many memorable moments: Thom unable to take his "eye video" seriously during You And Whose Army?, messing up on it, laughing a lot, thanking us a lot, rocking out nonstop, it was all so much fun. I will remember this show for the rest of my life, much more than the crowded LA Bowl nights and more than the highway problems that kept me driving back to L.A. until 4am. Some people complained Like Spinning Plates was replaced by Videotape. Well I'm glad they played it how they did because we got all 10 songs from In Rainbows! It was life-changing beyond words. After Santa Barbara tonight, my life will certainly be complete!]]></comment>
<comment author="BW" timestamp="10:27 AM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Say boht hollywood shows and went down last night for Chula Show.  It was very good but I did not the sound overall was not as good as The Bowl, especially on Reckoner (seemed thoms voice was buried).  Loved it though... pyramid song a highlight as well as Jigsaw (they jammed on that version).  Bascically preferred Monday's reckoner as Johnny did the guitar work Monday but Thom did guitar strums Sunday and last night.  Overall I rate this show with Sunday and just a bit better overall... but Monday took the cake.... by far... lucky by the way was better last night so I don't know... it's hard to criticize this band but seeing three shows in 4 days gives an interesting perspective..... buy again, Monday was THE SHOW I will remember.... No santa Barbara for me, I am whipped and can't handle that late night drive.  

I fell asleep in the parking lot last night waiting for the cars to leave and then woke up only car in the lot... .funny!!!  got home at 3am.....sleeeppppppy]]></comment>
<comment author="Brian" timestamp="9:38 AM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[A surprising and solid effort by Radiohead.  This was my 4th show and while the bookend shows they did last time around in SD were a bit more satisfying this performance did not dissappoint.  The band was SO on and the energy was so positive.  A good mix of favorites and new stuff.  It's so easy to get lost in the music (in the best possible ways)...]]></comment>
<comment author="maashu" timestamp="12:24 AM [PST], Thursday, August 28, 2008"><![CDATA[Wow, wow, wow!  My 9th Radiohead show and another fantastic setlist.  I can't believe we got Talk Show Host two shows in a row.  I could listen to that song on repeat (and I never, ever say that).

I think the Monday LA show was a little more unique in a way, but Thom's voice was much stronger at the beginning of this set.  Paranoid Android was psychedelic as all hell, Nude was ethereal, Lucky was a great surprise, and EIIRP was leaps and bounds better than Monday.  Damn you, Radiohead.  I'll remember this one, like all of them, forever.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=664]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
