<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="10"><![CDATA[Illinois]]></locale>
<city id="6"><![CDATA[Chicago]]></city>
<venue id="96"><![CDATA[Hutchinson Field Grant Park]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Hutchinson+Field+Grant+Park</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Friday, August 01, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>652</previousshow>
<nextshow>635</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="3" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="4" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="5" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="6" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="7" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="8" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="9" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="10" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="11" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="12" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="13" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="14" id="17"><![CDATA[The Bends]]></track>
<track num="15" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="16" id="19"><![CDATA[Fake Plastic Trees]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="19" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="20" id="54"><![CDATA[Dollars & Cents]]></track>
<track num="21" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="22" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="75"><![CDATA[2&#43;2=5]]></track>
<track num="24" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[empeaks]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jrob]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[skabadelic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[foraminute10]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jindew2]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[annie33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[madaski29]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[medina79]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neekole]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Battering Room]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radiohead8989]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lucky Schnauzer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[arrowman]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[OMS]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dustbunny]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[FriedNaiveFog]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[usher]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[plasticnitrogen]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thefullearth]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fakeplasticme]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[colonelmustard]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[emagdnim015]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[topsyturvytown]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[johnwhen]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blazak]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[greenb42]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sweetcell]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mrpoptop]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[justinwallen]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dragula22]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Idaa]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rbarthjr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[airon00]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thisishappening19th]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<images>
<image member="suprefan" src="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/080801/img20735ko7_tmb.jpg" link="http://gallery.58hours.com/stash/080801/img20735ko7.jpg" title=" "/>
</images>
<comments>
<comment author="radioheadslut705" timestamp="3:40 PM [PST], Thursday, September 11, 2008"><![CDATA[now that the tour's over (by tour I just mean the most recent 16 North American shows) and I've had a look at all the setlists, here's why I think we were lucky and got one of the top 2 or 3 setlists:
*4 songs from OK Computer. most shows got 3, one got only 2. and we got Airbag, which was the least frequently performed song from that album.
*excellent selections from The Bends. Fake Plastic Trees brought a tear to my eye
*one of only 2 times they played 2+2=5
*we got Idioteque, National Anthem, and Paranoid Android. none of these are rarities by any means, but they got skipped sometimes so they shouldn't be taken for granted.
*Dollars & Cents. enough said.
*we did NOT get Go Slowly or In Limbo. I realize not everyone will feel this way but those are probably the only 2 songs by Radiohead that I don't really care for.

so there you go. If anyone's still looking at this page at all, please feel free to agree/disagree/expand on this]]></comment>
<comment author="Gmck13" timestamp="12:25 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 06, 2008"><![CDATA[After waiting 8 hours in the same spot to see radiohead up front i was expecting an amazing show. But I didnt expect it to be as amazing as it was. It started out slow in my opinion as im not a huge fan of airbag or there there. But once they played nude things started to pick up a bit. No surprises was amazing and jigsaw blew me away. Lucky and the bends were incredible. And my favorite song ever fake plastic trees nearly brought me to tears. Videotape was amazing and paranoid android ripped my face off. And the last two songs were incredible. Best concert of my life. I love radiohead but i wasnt quite convinced they were the best band in the world. Now that ive seen them live im starting to think otherwise. Amazing Amazing Amazing. Best live band ever!!!!!!!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="sham" timestamp="2:17 PM [PST], Tuesday, August 05, 2008"><![CDATA[National Anthem, Jigsaw, Paranoid, 2+2=5 & Idioteque encore, body snatchers, 15 step intro to airbag, fake plastic trees, 

all with the new light system in the cleanest and most beautiful city in america. 

tens of thousands of people in awe for the 2 greatest bands in the world (radiohead & rage against the machine)...hands down the greatest festival ever...Lollapalooza 2008]]></comment>
<comment author="RTM" timestamp="10:35 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[Radiohead rocked my world as usual, despite me having a group of drunken scream-along-with-the-song idiots just behind me. Enough about them though. Of the 3 times I've seen Radiohead live, I think I enjoyed this setlist the most. It was a perfect mix of the old and the new. I really, really loved the new LED lighting system that I'd heard so much about. It brought a whole other dimension to the music, and dare I say made it even better? I loved the whole show (of course); with 15 Step, Jigsaw Falling Into Place, Fake Plastic Trees, There There and Paranoid Android as just some of my favorites. I just can't wait to see them next time they come around Chicago again. ]]></comment>
<comment author="radioheadslut705" timestamp="12:44 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[2nd time I've seen them, 1st was five years ago. Awesome show, beautiful venue, and the biggest sea of people I've ever been a part of. My friends I stayed with in Chicago said that fireworks are set off by the city every Friday night, and that it was just a coincidence that they went off during the set. But if it was just a coincidence, how on earth did the fireworks show have its grand finale going off exactly as Fake Plastic Trees was reaching its huge climax? Probably the most transcendent thing I've ever seen, I actually cried a little bit. Other highlights for me included Bodysnatchers, Airbag, Jigsaw, EverythingIIRPlace, Nat'l Anthem, 2+2=5...well pretty much the whole freakin show. I'll never forget it.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=634]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
