<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="1"><![CDATA[California]]></locale>
<city id="1"><![CDATA[Los Angeles]]></city>
<venue id="105"><![CDATA[Hollywood Bowl]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Hollywood+Bowl</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Friday, September 26, 2003</showdate>
<tour id="9"><![CDATA[Hail To The Thief]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>387</previousshow>
<nextshow>391</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Supergrass]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="75"><![CDATA[2&#43;2=5]]></track>
<track num="2" id="93"><![CDATA[Sit Down. Stand Up.]]></track>
<track num="3" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="4" id="39"><![CDATA[Kid A]]></track>
<track num="5" id="138"><![CDATA[Backdrifts]]></track>
<track num="6" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="7" id="23"><![CDATA[My Iron Lung]]></track>
<track num="8" id="52"><![CDATA[I Might Be Wrong]]></track>
<track num="9" id="6"><![CDATA[Creep]]></track>
<track num="10" id="60"><![CDATA[Sail To The Moon]]></track>
<track num="11" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="12" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="13" id="28"><![CDATA[Punch Up At a Wedding]]></track>
<track num="14" id="94"><![CDATA[Go To Sleep]]></track>
<track num="15" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="16" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="17" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="18" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="19" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="20" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="21" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="22" id="19"><![CDATA[Fake Plastic Trees]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="24" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[brian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Covebum]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[adelaney]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[black_star42]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jessica]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[industry71]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[superjen83]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[yalzin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Mad Clown]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jsandler]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[debaser]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardhead]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jas282]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pizzmoe]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Tabooty]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[knphilli]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Bort]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pzykotic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pao]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blueplaydoh]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[joshuamm2]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radioreverie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[taurina]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jdsaciv]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radiohead8989]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[BellyofaWhale]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jeffreysig]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dymo23]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[daviddi33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thefullearth]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fakeplasticme]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[scatterbrain83]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dubstar]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardlylurkin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mahntoh]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[piz]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blackmonolith]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cygnus7]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[onablankshore9]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dennisdster]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[joebaca64]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[Show was updated in real-time by 58hours staff at the Bowl (via web-enabled phone)
<ul>
<li>An abbreviated version of Big Ideas was played - although it did not appear on the band's official setlist.  (Thom alone on acoustic guitar)
<li>the official band setlist also listed the first encore finale as Fake Plastic Trees/How To Disappear.  Apparently the band chose to go with Fake Plastic
<li>Thom dedicated Airbag to "the Chili Peppers"
</ul>]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="Scott" timestamp="4:25 PM [PST], Tuesday, September 30, 2003"><![CDATA[i'm doing a cover story on radiohead for URB magazine and saw all three shows they played this week (shoreline and both h bowl shows) and tonight's show was easily the best. while i really enjoyed the looseness of the shoreline show (colin later called it a 'rubber-legged'  gig), but the 2nd of the bowl shows was probably the best show i've seen them do (i've i seen quite a few at this point!). 

the only thing i can add to this thread that hasn't already been covered was the outrageous celebrity quotient of both LA shows. thursday was pretty average (biggest celeb sighting: elijah wood, coolest celeb sighting: beck)), but friday was insane. i saw everyone from meg ryan to daryl hannah to the chili peppers to butch vig (who had nothing but praises for the show), dj shadow, paul oakenfold, chris martin & gwyneth paltrow, robert downey jr, haley joel osmond - the list goes on. but the best sighting of the night was seeing alison janney (of the west wing) dancing furiously and singing along to pretty much every song - spoke to her later and it turns out she's a HUGE fan. 

OK, that's all for now. watch for the dec issue of URB magazine for the full story - i did a really nice interview w/thom in LA - really good stuff!


Hope that wasn't too off topic...




]]></comment>
<comment author="Lynne" timestamp="3:46 PM [PST], Tuesday, September 30, 2003"><![CDATA[Brilliance may be difficult to describe, but we all know it when we see it - one part talent, two parts wisdom and three parts passion.  Kuddos to Radiohead - truly a brilliant performance on Friday night. Talent is a flame; genius is a fire.  Keep it going.  True innovators are inevitably controversial - love that about you guys. Long live Radiohead. Peace.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="howard" timestamp="5:19 PM [PST], Monday, September 29, 2003"><![CDATA[they should have a balloting system where everyone can vote on what they want to hear.  i would have like to have heard street spirit and exit music.  or anything from the bends for that matter.  i guess that is why you should go to every show you can in the tri-state area.]]></comment>
<comment author="Alen S." timestamp="3:15 AM [PST], Monday, September 29, 2003"><![CDATA[Didn't see Supergrass (I would have liked to, but, you know..)Found our seats on time and waited dilligently for Radiohead to begin.Wow.Oh My.I kept yelling "CREEP!!!" over and over between songs...and...they played it! So everyone knows now that they played creep because of me... Ha.Really though, excellent excellent show.You guys were there...You know.Couldn't have had a better Birthday present.]]></comment>
<comment author="Alen S." timestamp="3:14 AM [PST], Monday, September 29, 2003"><![CDATA[Oh and in addition they played no surprises, Idioteque and (not to mention) creep... the songs i wanted to hear the most! Truly, it was such a surprise when they played creep, i totally was joking when i was telling my friend that i knew that they would.XD
"The Gloaming" was really a surprise."You and whose army" was delightful, and having a pair of binoculars really helped to see what the band was doing collectively to keep up the energy. That night showed me that seeing a great band live is really the only way to do it at all.
FOREVERFOREVERFOREVERFOREVER.]]></comment>
<comment author="jason" timestamp="1:56 AM [PST], Monday, September 29, 2003"><![CDATA[OK, I love radiohead, but this show made me obsessed with radiohead.  I can't stop thinking about this show!  The multimedia was fantastic and fit very well to each song.  Can anyone remember what they did for each song...such as which song had the red footage of Thom with the time stamp on it, etc?]]></comment>
<comment author="colleen" timestamp="2:59 PM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[that show was fucking amazing! but now every other concer i ever see is going to suck becuase this one was so superb. it was almost a religious experience to have everyone singing "creep" together. even though the band hates that, it was amazing. simply amazing.]]></comment>
<comment author="kid C" timestamp="2:48 PM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[amazing. everything from the light wall to the video synching made for an amzing show. I really felt like I witnessed somethign special last night. The hightlight was Thom playing to the camera on "whose Army" and a not-so-pop Creep with a heavenly wail from Thom. The only song missing for me was "sardines"]]></comment>
<comment author="CeeEL" timestamp="2:07 PM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[The greatest night ever!! I am so lucky to have scored last minute tickets and arriving to a setlist worth flying around the world for.  Also would like to thank 58hours.com for their wonderful and unique real time updating.  It makes me wish we could send them to ever gigs so that they can update setlists for the next 30 years. heh!!!! ROCK ON!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="Bryan" timestamp="3:39 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[This was the best live show I have ever seen.  The band is absolutely amazing and everything they did made me speechless throughout the show.  Thom's energy is great.]]></comment>
<comment author="thom" timestamp="3:21 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[i'll make this short. the band was in top form. johnny's guitar was on fire, especially his pickups. ed's guitar wasn't loud enough. the set list was amazing. the gloaming was actually one of the most interesting songs of the night.and supergrass kicked ass, especially when they played a rendition of NEIL YOUNG's "the loner." i doubt anyone knew which song that was, so i thought i'd educate some of y'all.

p.s. i didn't see creep coming from a mile away.]]></comment>
<comment author="richard" timestamp="1:41 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[radiohead played superbly tonight. jonny was spectacular.  it was great to hear my iron lung, and pulling out creep blew me away. the lighting for the gloaming perfectly set the mood for the song.  and this was my very first radiohead show.  i feel very privileged.  these guys are so cool.]]></comment>
<comment author="curelover" timestamp="1:19 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[AMAZING. that was the word for tonight's show. the setlist yesterday was a bit disappointing but tonight's show more than made up for it. i loved how they played my iron lung, i might be wrong, morning bell and no surprises. all the guys were in good moods. johnny is mind blowing on the guitar ... seriously the boy is very very talented. thom is one of the best dancers out there. i wonder if he got some of his moves from michael stipe. hee hee. the audience this time was much more into the music and really responsive. well at least in the J section. i looked down at the pit and they seemed a bit dead during some songs. not sure though cause i was pretty far ... ha ha. wonderful show ..... radiohead knows how to ROCK !!!!!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="jc" timestamp="1:17 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[big ideas only an intro, best i've seen em technically speaking. best for me: kid a, end of the gloaming, thom crazy dancing on many song tonight but didnt talk much, didnt say much, airbag dedicated to chili peppers, seemed like thom motioned to the crowd when he said it suggesting they were there, johnny really was amazing]]></comment>
<comment author="Adam" timestamp="1:08 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[WOW! What an incredible evening. Positive energy. Wonderful setlist. My Iron Lung, Creep, No Surprises, Fake plastic treeeeees. yeehah. Thom was spectacular but I can't get over Johnny. I love the sounds he makes. He must have great music going through his head all the time. Whether he's on guitar or fiddling with machines it always comes up urgent and unique. I have been blown away, this was one of the best shows I've seen. I know this is stupid but I never realized there were words to Kid A. Thought it was computers moaning. What an incredible response from an L.A. audience. I can't wait for the New Orleans show but truth be told we're going for the food.]]></comment>
<comment author="Tony" timestamp="12:56 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[WOW.  that is an understatement.  this show was abso-fucking-lutely incredible.  the setlist was perfect, the encores were amazing and the song selection was from so many different albums, it was so GREAT !!! Thom was extra spasmy tonight especially during the second encore.  The ending with everything in its right place was worth going to radiohead concerts FOREVERFOREVERFOREVER.  i liked how they all walked off stage when they felt they were done adding their piece to the song.  GREAT SHOW.]]></comment>
<comment author="Amanda" timestamp="12:27 AM [PST], Saturday, September 27, 2003"><![CDATA[2nd night was absolutly awesome.  Crowd interaction was definatly more pumped tonight.  Thom's camera playing during 'You and Who's Army?' was cool.  Glad they ended with 'Everything in it's Right Place' again.  This has to be the #1 best show of the entire year; hands down.  Tonight's show goes on the record books.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="jeff" timestamp="11:47 PM [PST], Friday, September 26, 2003"><![CDATA[just got back, holy shit...just look at the setlist.  seen radiohead several times before, never saw creep. gloaming, idioteque and fake plastic trees were worth the flight from oregon by themselves. i love this band.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=388]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
