<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="3"><![CDATA[New York]]></locale>
<city id="4"><![CDATA[New York City]]></city>
<venue id="97"><![CDATA[Madison Square Garden]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Madison+Square+Garden</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Friday, October 10, 2003</showdate>
<tour id="9"><![CDATA[Hail To The Thief]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>398</previousshow>
<nextshow>403</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Low]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="2" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="3" id="75"><![CDATA[2&#43;2=5]]></track>
<track num="4" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="5" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="6" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="7" id="89"><![CDATA[Myxomatosis]]></track>
<track num="8" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="9" id="44"><![CDATA[In Limbo]]></track>
<track num="10" id="60"><![CDATA[Sail To The Moon]]></track>
<track num="11" id="6"><![CDATA[Creep]]></track>
<track num="12" id="88"><![CDATA[Scatterbrain]]></track>
<track num="13" id="94"><![CDATA[Go To Sleep]]></track>
<track num="14" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="15" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="16" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="17" id="93"><![CDATA[Sit Down. Stand Up.]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="19" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="20" id="28"><![CDATA[Punch Up At a Wedding]]></track>
<track num="21" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="22" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="23" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="24" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hailtotheleaf]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rdtyphn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[crp640]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[peterpan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ejdanielson]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[philip]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ajacks10]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[popartist]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pearly1357]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chokedamp]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tubro]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[veggy_head]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rysears]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[wheremysubsidies]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[toad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dreamsie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fradleybox]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[zara.]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mrdennis]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[kevcon]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[htttocac]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[kida1977]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[randyrad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[karmafifi]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lsylv]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[agentonze]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Battering Room]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chokedamp1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chules]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lucky Schnauzer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[daviddi33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[kupfer21]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ryansearson]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[leifdog222]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[andrewudin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pure]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[trojanpony]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[gberg]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[paulallynloomis@gmail.com]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blazak]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tracer123]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chokedamp123]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Number 6]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[beaucolburn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sauce]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[binky the doormat]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hardlylurkin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Kid Julian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[stefanglidden]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dragula22]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[joebaca64]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rbarthjr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chipymac]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[Setlist was updated in real-time by 58hours staff.]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="adrian" timestamp="2:34 PM [PST], Monday, May 03, 2004"><![CDATA[this was my first radiohead concert. the kinetic energy of thom's singing & dancing, the amazing light show, the incredible response of the crowd made for an experience that i couldn't have dreamt of while listening to their music on my headphones. i'm from nyc. so the element of surprise [evidenced by the over-zealous fan who climbed on the stage to dance around thom] was a unique 'ny-only-thing' that i ain't gonna soon forget. btw, the young fan was quickly escorted off the stage by the hard-working security staff, rest assured that the fab-five were unharmed. loved the way ppl cheered after thom sang the very relevant lines, 'bring down the government, they don't, they don't speak for us,' off of 'No Surprises.' not many other bands out there can give you euphoria, ethereal, morose, defiant, & political activism. 'head can do it all & i think they're atkins-friendly too even though thom's a vegan [?] ]]></comment>
<comment author="jen" timestamp="3:19 PM [PST], Tuesday, October 28, 2003"><![CDATA[this show was AMAZING!!!!!!!  need i say more?  okay, i'll say more.  the next show i'll see will have a lot to live up to.  honestly.  thom has such a great sense of humor - i loved his whole schtick with "you and whose army".  and though "creep" hasn't one of my favorite radiohead songs, listening to it live just won me over.  i have to say that everything just gelled that night.  not only was the band great, but the fans were awesome too.  i mean a concert isn't great unless the fans go wild, and i'd have to say that the entire night was an electrifying experience.]]></comment>
<comment author="james" timestamp="3:19 PM [PST], Wednesday, October 15, 2003"><![CDATA[great show; not to be a stickler, but correct altered creep lyrics were:

'want a perfect body / so i could - look good next to you'

coulda done w a little less HttT]]></comment>
<comment author="Tyler" timestamp="10:52 AM [PST], Tuesday, October 14, 2003"><![CDATA[I thought the show was better than anything I could have ever imagined.  I don't think it could have been possible for "You and Whose Army" to have been performed any better than it was.  I was also amazed that I got to hear "Creep" live because I thought it was something i would never get to hear (by the way the altered lyric was "I want a perfect body/ So I can lie naked next to you."  Paranoid Android was incredible as was Street Spirit and Just.  "Idiotechque" was mindblowing.   I was a little dissapointed by the shortage of songs off Amnesiac but the general mix was great.  Radiohead is definately the best live band around and Thom is definately the coolest lead singer.]]></comment>
<comment author="jim" timestamp="6:20 PM [PST], Monday, October 13, 2003"><![CDATA[wow...i was 5 feet from the stage and it was such a great concert..the band seemed to flow with this energy and the audience just fed off of it..amazing]]></comment>
<comment author="Marbles" timestamp="1:49 PM [PST], Monday, October 13, 2003"><![CDATA[This show was {flipping through un abridged dictionary for the correct adjective} prodigious. I've seen the band several times before, but had never seen them perform Creep before. I was excited to hear it, but the highlight was definately Street Spirit. That song brings tears to my eyes, and once again, it didn't fail to achieve that goal. Thom's performance of You and Whose Army? was incredible! The eerie faces and creepy grimaces that he made into the camera were one of the most memorable performances of that song that I've ever seen, or of any song that I've ever seen live... and I've been to MANY concerts. The little hairs on my back and the small of my neck are still standing up on end. Amazing show, incredible performances... the flashing "FOREVER" at the end of the show tricked me... I missed part of it (or so I thought) and was under the impression it said "GOODBYE FOREVER FOREVER FOREVER FOREVER... " and I had tears welling in my eyes until I realized I was wrong. ]]></comment>
<comment author="Homesick Alien" timestamp="11:06 AM [PST], Monday, October 13, 2003"><![CDATA[Great show!  2nd time seeing Radiohead live.   I agree that the Hail To The Thief material worked really well live, but I think 10 songs (out of 24 total in the show) from that CD was a bit excessive.   Yeah, I love the new stuff, but there were so many older songs I would have liked -- so I supposed in my opinion the show could have had a more balanced set list.  Still, it was an amazing performance!]]></comment>
<comment author="pete" timestamp="8:11 PM [PST], Sunday, October 12, 2003"><![CDATA[show was killer, my first too. setlist was all i'd hoped for although i would've loved to hear some stuff off amnesiac like knives out. i also would've loved to hear iron lung, which is one of my all-time faves. the correct 'altered lyric' to creep was 'i want a perfect body....so i could, look good next to you.' i loved hearing creep no matter what anyone says; loved hearing street spirit; loved hearing lucky. man it was all good. my ideal concert would be them playing almost every singly song they've put out, including b-sides.

bottom line: this is the best band together today, the best band since the beatles. they rock, and seeing them live at some point is a must for any fan. an experience i will live with forever!]]></comment>
<comment author="Dee" timestamp="8:32 PM [PST], Saturday, October 11, 2003"><![CDATA[What an amazing show!!!!! The best way I can describe it, it was a very spiritual experience for me.  The music grabbed hold of me, reached in and captivated my soul!  I left in awe and craving more.  Sadly, they didn't play one of my favorites, True Love Waits.  I still felt blessed to have experienced all that was shared with us...]]></comment>
<comment author="Joshua King" timestamp="9:38 AM [PST], Saturday, October 11, 2003"><![CDATA[Also my first time seeing the band live, though I've waited many years to do so.  In a word: magical.  It was a surreal and mind-blowing experience.]]></comment>
<comment author="R" timestamp="7:00 AM [PST], Saturday, October 11, 2003"><![CDATA[I'm so happy I ended up at this show instead of the one the night before.  Set list couldn't have been any better for me (loved all the OK Computer), and although Creep sounded great, I could have done without it (am I the only one that doesn't really associate Creep with Radiohead?).  Anyway, amazing.]]></comment>
<comment author="Emperor Wilson" timestamp="6:56 AM [PST], Saturday, October 11, 2003"><![CDATA[I've only seen radiohead once before, and I thought this show was a bit weaker.  It seemed to be lacking a degree of energy.  However, when the band came out for the encores, the volume was taken up a notch and the band seemed to be more charged.  Overall it was like a freight train, it started very slow, but as the night went on it really picked up and became a powerful show.
     Throughout the show, Thom would break into some rave dancing that really seemed to get the crowd going.  We were "treated" to a performance of creep, with an altered lyric, something like "I want a perfect body, so I can see it lying next to you."  I'd really like to see them do something completely different with this song.  
So, overall, I thought it turned out to be a very good show.  I am just adding the downside because nobody ever seems to be critical.  
With the exception of Paranoid Android, which sounded like a complete mess, the songs were all very good.  I particularly liked the live bass line to the gloaming, one of my least favorite radiohead songs.  It gave it a new life. They are very good at making their songs work live.]]></comment>
<comment author="Jamie Packer" timestamp="11:08 PM [PST], Friday, October 10, 2003"><![CDATA[Incredible show.  First time seeing Radiohead and they blew me away.  Tons of energy brought to every song.  Great setlist, particularly Street Spirit and Just.  Paranoid Android was unbelievable.  Songs from Hail To The Thief were completely transformed live.  Great experience.  ]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=399]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
