<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="131"><![CDATA[Indiana]]></locale>
<city id="261"><![CDATA[Indianapolis]]></city>
<venue id="477"><![CDATA[Verizon Wireless Music Center]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Verizon+Wireless+Music+Center</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Sunday, August 03, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>634</previousshow>
<nextshow>636</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
<track num="3" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="4" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="5" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="6" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="7" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="8" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="9" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="10" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="11" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="12" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="13" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="14" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="15" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="16" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="17" id="41"><![CDATA[How To Disappear Completely]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="19" id="156"><![CDATA[Bangers and Mash]]></track>
<track num="20" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="21" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="22" id="2"><![CDATA[Karma Police]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="24" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="25" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[skabadelic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[annie33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neekole]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radiohead8989]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[JoshuaB81285]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dualingeyes]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dustbunny]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ruddtherudd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sakerocket1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[brickmyers]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dirk Gently]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[fakeplasticme]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[matt wallen]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sweeti3742]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[casbomb1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mrhardin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[emagdnim015]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[topsyturvytown]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Idaa]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[gloamdroid57]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thisishappening19th]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="Alan Welch" timestamp="7:29 PM [PST], Wednesday, September 17, 2008"><![CDATA[Amazing show, I was at the Charlotte, NC and there was no comparison. I may have been a little too drunk in Charlotte, but the Indianapolis show was mind boggling. It was as if I chose the setlist. The Gloaming melted my face off, Climbing Up the Walls never hurt anyone, and Street Spirit really tied the room together. I had enough party favors to make the whole day/night amazing. The campground across the street made for one hell of a trip. I hope Radiohead comes back again next year.]]></comment>
<comment author="Teresa" timestamp="11:04 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my first Radiohead show ever, and i was truly moved.
Absolutely, monumentally beautiful.]]></comment>
<comment author="Zachary" timestamp="7:50 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[amazing show. my first radiohead show and i wouldnt of had it any other way...well maybe optimistic, go to sleep, or let down(my three favorite songs) haha but hey the setlist was great, they played great and flowed really freaking well. all i hope is they tour next summer cause il be planning a few trips to a few shows...wonderful concert and by far the best concert ive been too.]]></comment>
<comment author="Thay Guy" timestamp="2:32 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[Loved the show,... got tickets last minute (Thanks Rick and Jackie!!)  wonderful not to have to drive for hours to see them,.... hope they come back to Indy again next year!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="Nick" timestamp="1:17 PM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[My first show - it was absolutely incredible. I was in the first row on the lawn, and the crowd was so into it - it was a giant dancefest, especially Idioteque through Just and the first two. The new intro to EEIIRP (a beta band cover) was really cool, and the radio noises before TNA rocked.]]></comment>
<comment author="Ian" timestamp="10:54 AM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my first Radiohead show and of course they amazed me every minute.  All of the "ballads" were so moving, the electronic songs were gritty and raucous, and the more rocking numbers did just that - rock.  I've only been to a dozen or so national act concerts, but I know it will be hard to find any light show as amazing as I saw last night.  The lights matched up with the mood and the timing and the lyrics of each song perfectly.  Then of course the band played the most amazing set of songs any fan could ask for! I'm so glad In Rainbows was so well represented, these gents have certainly worked hard to get to where they are today, and they deserve all the props in the world. All hail Radiohead!]]></comment>
<comment author="Melanie" timestamp="8:55 AM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[Last nights show was just unbelievable. Pyramid Song live last night was just unreal.]]></comment>
<comment author="Chad Nettleman" timestamp="7:50 AM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[Incredible show.  Band was lively and Thom seemed to be having a great time.  The weather was amazing as well.]]></comment>
<comment author="Jeff" timestamp="6:53 AM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[Last night was my first Radiohead show.  It was sweet, all the songs were well played and the new material was awesome live.  Deer Creek rocks!]]></comment>
<comment author="Redsrule" timestamp="4:30 AM [PST], Monday, August 04, 2008"><![CDATA[Great show, Great crowd.  1st time seeing Radiohead since Red Rocks 2001.  Wish I had had closer seats.  Radiohead is one band that is fun to actually watch them play...so much going on with every song.  Unfortunately I didn't get an Airbag or Paranoid Android, but I'm not complaining.  Light show was fantastic!!  ]]></comment>
<comment author="todd, madison wi" timestamp="10:50 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[Saw them in atlanta in may and this was ten times the show.  They felt rushed in Atlanta and here Thom really seemed to be in a good groove and enjoying himself.  The band rocked, sounded great and had excellent energy and rapport with the audience.  Yorke was awesome, Jonny played the guitar parts to Just very similar to the record but wailed on it.  Jigsaw was amazing.  They nailed Weird Fishes and Jigsaw unlike any other live versions i've seen or heard anywhere.  Thom looked at Jonny after Faust Arp and smiled one of those 'that was incredible' smiles that makes everyone want to be able to be on stage.  They genuinely seemed to be enhouing themselves on every song.  I've seen U2, REM, the Who, Rush, Floyd, the Clash and 50 other great bands live and this was one of the most energetic shows i've seen,]]></comment>
<comment author="Brian Shoemake" timestamp="10:04 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[Amazing performance! I can only hope to see them again in the future. There is nobody like Radiohead. That is the best concert I have ever seen.]]></comment>
<comment author="Joe from Pittsburgh" timestamp="9:07 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[Flippin' sweet set! I'm going to see them in Cleveland tomorrow, and am stoked beyond belief!]]></comment>
<comment author="Chris" timestamp="9:07 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[They dropped Paranoid Android, but closing with Street Spirit is pretty cool, I'm hoping they will play Airbag in New York, and I'd do anything to hear Killer Cars which is highly doubtful]]></comment>
<comment author="LameO Dushame" timestamp="7:28 PM [PST], Sunday, August 03, 2008"><![CDATA[I am on Phone, and all I know is on first encore Starts with: 

You And Who's Army,
Banger's And Mash.
 
That's all I know, but I do know.  It sounds fucking great, full of energy and fresh to the road.  

I just seen them at Lallapalooza and the show was amazing.  I am just getting home and not really soaked the whole experience and don't know what to say about it besides, It was a strange and rocking awesome weekend..  Would I do it again?  I don't know.  For Radiohead once again then yes.  HA HA HA HA!!!!!  ]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=635]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
