<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="5"><![CDATA[Portugal]]></country>
<locale id="47"><![CDATA[Oporto]]></locale>
<city id="71"><![CDATA[Oporto]]></city>
<venue id="114"><![CDATA[Coliseu do Porto]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Coliseu+do+Porto</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Friday, July 26, 2002</showdate>
<shownavi><previousshow>220</previousshow>
<nextshow>222</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Four Tet]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="2" id="88"><![CDATA[Scatterbrain]]></track>
<track num="3" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="4" id="89"><![CDATA[Myxomatosis]]></track>
<track num="5" id="60"><![CDATA[Sail To The Moon]]></track>
<track num="6" id="119"><![CDATA[Up on the Ladder]]></track>
<track num="7" id="68"><![CDATA[Lift]]></track>
<track num="8" id="52"><![CDATA[I Might Be Wrong]]></track>
<track num="9" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="10" id="23"><![CDATA[My Iron Lung]]></track>
<track num="11" id="44"><![CDATA[In Limbo]]></track>
<track num="12" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="13" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="14" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="15" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="16" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="17" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="18" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="19" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="20" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="21" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="22" id="19"><![CDATA[Fake Plastic Trees]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="93"><![CDATA[Sit Down. Stand Up.]]></track>
<track num="24" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
</encore2>
<encore3>
<track num="25" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]]></track>
<track num="26" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]]></track>
</encore3>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[peterpan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Jarly]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[royshearer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mandyr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lost-child]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[zara.]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radioreverie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Tweed]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[optimistic]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bigdaddy]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Geox]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="Roy Shearer" timestamp="10:53 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 04, 2004"><![CDATA[Just back from a great holiday in Europe with the unimaginably amazing climax of attending both radiohead gigs in the Coliseu do Porto. The best holiday ever topped by possibly the best night of my life on the 27th, no joke!

Firstly, there is an error in your setlist for the 27th july gig. Between 'I Might be Wrong' and 'In Limbo' was 'Morning Bell'. Secondly, I have a very good recording of the gig on the 27th but don't know whether to upload it. Would anyone really want it? I don't have alot of webspace you see.

Finally, you don't appear to have any reviews of either Porto gigs so here are my offerings, edit at will [you cant expect me to brief about these enormous events]:

26.7.2
5pm. There was an excited buzz in the crowd that queued for hours in the sun outside the magnificent art deco Coliseum. Rumours of the new songs and the apparent success of the 2nd night in Lisbon mixed with the happy chatter flitting around in various languages.

9pm. Right up at the front we listen to the support that we dub twolaptopsandasampler. Its interesting soundmongery but could really do with some visuals to liven up the act in a live setting. Nevertheless a little of my imroptu break dancing does the trick...

10pm. Finally. The 'head take the stage and there is the engulfing sense of everyones anxiety being released. There is a noticibly large rack of guitars off stage to the left and an even more conspicuous 'lost in space'esque flashing console lurking near Johnny... The 7 new songs are eagerly enjoyed - new to the ears but with enough of that x factor to be instantly memorable. Thom is sympathetic to the audience, joking that there is 'not long to go now' followed by a hammy yawn. He appears to be on top form, or maybe its because we're only a matter of feet away from him that we relish his every expression. Some great seemingly deranged dancing [we know theres method to his madness] and smirking at the crowd. Later on, while Thom plays the piano intro to 'You and Whose Army' someone at the back persists in screaming. He interrupts the sensitive vocal line to have a little chuckle to himself and subdues the screamer with a look that just says, "thankyou but really, not now..." Some of the new songs are unintroduced including one with a great drumming outro from Phil. Those that are introduced are not without irony. Keep the Wolf From the Door: "This is a song about the plague, one of my favourite subjects." Myxomatosis: "This is also about the plague, its called Myxomatosis, whoo!" The night proceeds into more familiar territory, we in the crowd not quite believing our luck at hearing all the songs we have idolised on CD for so long. A privilege, climaxing in us all freaking out to 'Just'. As for 'fade
out', there couldn't be a more apt end to the night.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=221]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
