<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="1"><![CDATA[California]]></locale>
<city id="1"><![CDATA[Los Angeles]]></city>
<venue id="105"><![CDATA[Hollywood Bowl]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Hollywood+Bowl</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Sunday, August 24, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>661</previousshow>
<nextshow>663</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="3" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="4" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="5" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="6" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="7" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="8" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="9" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="10" id="92"><![CDATA[Wolf at the Door]]></track>
<track num="11" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="12" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="13" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="14" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="15" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="16" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
<track num="17" id="41"><![CDATA[How To Disappear Completely]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="19" id="54"><![CDATA[Dollars & Cents]]></track>
<track num="20" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="21" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
<track num="22" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="24" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="25" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Covebum]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[adelaney]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jessica]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ronho66]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[polystyrened]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dleach31]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[debaser]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[suprefan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lucky1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Tabooty]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Bort]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pao]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neekole]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[wierdfishee]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jreedmiller]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Lucky Schnauzer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[BellyofaWhale]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jeffreysig]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dhsuguitan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dymo23]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lardlad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pure]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[robs]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[thefullearth]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[black-eyedangel]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[johnwhen]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[scatterbrain83]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[nickdavey]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sweetcell]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[swimnmex]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mrpoptop]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sauce]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[redsoxfaan3]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[stefanglidden]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[piz]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blackmonolith]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jakeadamyork]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jrsdthird]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[cybelle]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[DOPIATE]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[shawndowns]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[onablankshore9]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sukjin]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jpc79]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[josh_day]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[diztorted]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Mstetten]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chaos_lynn]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[michaelmirra]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rbarthjr]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[htdc_jen]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[A recording of this show is available at: http://www.glidemagazine.com/hiddentrack/exclusive-audio-radiohead-hollywood-bowl/]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="Shawn" timestamp="7:14 PM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song was truly unbelievable. Great show.]]></comment>
<comment author="radio_h_ead_junkie951" timestamp="1:11 PM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my very first Radiohead show. Every time I wanted to see them before, tickets sold out or something came up.

Anywho, I thought this was probably the best live show I have EVER been to. The music was perfect, Thom's voice was awesome, and the crowd was really into it. 

There was a lady sitting by me who's name is Andrea and she went there by herself and was returning to Monday's show again (lucky her).

Highlight would have to be Videotape, Paranoid Android, Exit Music (for a film), and Nude. I can't explain how excellent Thom's voice was.

The light show and still video shots were awesome. The video had a kind of cartoonish look which came across very well.

Only con was I wish I would have taken someone different with me. ]]></comment>
<comment author="Colleen" timestamp="12:33 PM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[I have to agree with some of the others: the set list was a little on the slow side, but otherwise a great show. Highlights for me: Jigsaw..., Lucky, Paranoid Android, Street Spirit (goof up and all). Didn't catch any celebrities - and I had front row terrace box seats. Going tonight; hoping for Let Down - I have NEVER heard it live and it's my favorite Radiohead song ever.]]></comment>
<comment author="Arvin Bautista" timestamp="12:04 PM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[The sound was way tight and they played impeccably, better than I've ever heard them before (during the HTTT tours), and the two times Thom fouled up it was more charming than anything.

However, the setlist wasn't particularly inspired, and from the middle rear the sound seemed low. It didn't help that the section I sat in insisted on sitting still for most of the set. Tamest audience for a Radiohead show EVER. You'd think given how many slow songs they played the audience would get up when they played Idioteque or Bodysnatchers, but even the people who stood up didn't even bother swaying back and forth.

Oh, and visually it was definitely one of if not the best looking concert I'd ever seen.]]></comment>
<comment author="ronho66" timestamp="11:12 AM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[I will have to agree with thesellman's account - not spectacular, but solid.  My wife and I showed up early since we were without tickets for the first time for any concert - shutout at WASTE and regular sale.  We were rewarded by some kind soul who sold his extras at face value - bless you my man - you made our night.  We enjoyed the new green-concious tube lighting and backdrop lighting. What about the flub on Street Spirit?  We were too far away to see how/why that went down.  I can't imagine that ever happening before or again, but loved that Thom asked if they should continue and then brought it home.  The new stuff sounded sharp, tight and spot on.  I only hope that they might loosen it up a bit and break something out similar to the In Limbo from the Vancouver show.  Perhaps Knives Out? I know, I know, I'm dreaming.  In summation, another solid show from the greatest act on this or any other planet.]]></comment>
<comment author="K" timestamp="10:32 AM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[nothing short of amazing. highlight for me was paranoid android. sound was spot on. everyone all around just seemed to be in a great mood, but then again, why wouldnt you be. Christina Aguilera and husband, Diane Lane, Heather Graham, Balthazar Getty, and Bradley Cooper were the ones I saw. ]]></comment>
<comment author="thesellman" timestamp="9:34 AM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[Solid effort - nothing spectacular from my perspective on the set list front.  But, then again, an average / solid show from Radiohead beats pretty much anything else out there right now.  I wish Friday's set from SF had been played at the Hollywood Bowl given how terrible the venue-related issues were at the Outside Lands Festival.  Just makes me realize how special the 2006 mini tour was (i.e. the Greek Theater, etc.).  Though, I would imagine tonight will be sick as their second show at the Hollywood Bowl will provide opportunity to play some more non-In Rainbows tunes (which are all solid, BTW, its just not like the Grateful Dead where they mixed up everything every night so there is a bit of overload if you see too many shows on the same tour)...  wish work / reality would have allowed for a Monday show in L.A. rather than a Sunday (I imagine Air Bag, Fake Plastic Trees, Karma Police, Black Star, My Iron Lung, etc. are all strong possibilities tonight) but nevertheless I am grateful just to have been there.  Set list - 5/10; execution 8/10; venue 8/10 (just given that it wasn't Golden Gate Park gives it an extra bump there).  

BTW, lots of celebs given it was L.A. - sat next to Ron Howard, saw Lucy Liu (sp?), Justin Timberlake, Rick Rubin the producer (sp?), Maria Sharapova (sp?), Jason Mraz, Jason Bateman, Ellen Degeneress (sp?) and her new wife, etc. - I am not much of a star gazer but its cool to know that some of the most influential figures in entertainment are being influenced by what I think is the most historically significant band of my generation.]]></comment>
<comment author="hosereama" timestamp="8:14 AM [PST], Monday, August 25, 2008"><![CDATA[Kind of a *slow* show...seems like they've slowed down about 70% of the songs by at least 10bpm, but maybe thats just me. Good show, not great.

Soundcheck setlist:
Setlist for sck:
new song (rape me before they come?)
In limbo (intro)
optimistic
morning bell
go slowly
lucky (2nd verse and on) x2
there there
wolf at the door
idioteque (sings hey ya by outkast instead)
drums + bass goofoff]]></comment>
<comment author="Patrick" timestamp="11:40 PM [PST], Sunday, August 24, 2008"><![CDATA[sickest show. mellow sunday night vibe overall. the guys seemed really into it. Breathe and All I need were highlights. Reckoner in 1st Encore was great. They really jumped around through a lot of their albums. been a fan for 14 years and was VERY satisfied with tonight's show!]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=662]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
