<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="14"><![CDATA[Florida]]></locale>
<city id="258"><![CDATA[Tampa]]></city>
<venue id="468"><![CDATA[Ford Amphitheatre]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Ford+Amphitheatre</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Tuesday, May 06, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="11"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Spring) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>620</previousshow>
<nextshow>622</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Liars]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="2" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="3" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="4" id="156"><![CDATA[Bangers and Mash]]></track>
<track num="5" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="6" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="7" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="8" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="9" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="10" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="11" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="12" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="13" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="14" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="15" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="16" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
<track num="17" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="19" id="37"><![CDATA[The Tourist]]></track>
<track num="20" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="21" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="22" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="17"><![CDATA[The Bends]]></track>
<track num="24" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[aryall]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Bort]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[randyrad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radiohead8989]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ATLFalconsFAN]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[adam420]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[neobob187]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[hecate dracul]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dr. Jimmy]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[drock]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tampatrader]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Laura]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Gentso]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Arianna]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[plasticnitrogen]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="jermcc@gmail" timestamp="7:12 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 14, 2008"><![CDATA[orlano traffic's fun allysa.. =-P    =-( that's why i try not to drive here..

I just got this show and am about to listen to it!! The recording is said to sound great, and obviously this shows getting some great reviews!! ]]></comment>
<comment author="Matt" timestamp="2:35 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my 4th time at a RH show. Pretty good setlist with the huge my two personal favorite songs: Lucky and The Tourist. I've got Ok Computer on vinyl and the last side is almost worn out before the rest of the album is even broken in. They made me happy with that one. 

What's with House of Cards? It's just an alright song, and used as a closer it's very anticlamactic, especially following The Bends. Anyway I was in West Palm and Tampa, both times with good seats (1st row far right West Palm, 15th row far right Tampa), and have no regrets about ticket or travel prices.]]></comment>
<comment author="FaustArpeggi" timestamp="11:29 AM [PST], Friday, May 09, 2008"><![CDATA[Amazing show! I enjoyed it more than West Palm, not that West Palm was bad in any way. The sound was better and everything was tighter at Tampa. No Weird Fishes reprise tonight! Word has it that on the band's setlist, How to Disappear was in place of The Bends for the second encore. Nothing against Disappear (it was a definite highlight from West Palm), but I'm glad they called the audible.]]></comment>
<comment author="Dan" timestamp="9:48 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[This was by far the most incredible show I've ever been to. The band was spot on all night, and the sound quality was amazing out on the lawn. The light show was breathtaking, and the setlist was also very good. I thought Idioteque was my favorite of the night. This was my first Radiohead show and I hope there are more in the future! 
]]></comment>
<comment author="alyssaFL" timestamp="7:19 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[Everyone was into the concert. I was chilling out in section 8, well not really chilling out more look jumping around and swaying! ;) This concert was set up wonderful, the led lights and Thom had a wonderful personality, funny and charming! Best concert so far. They played so many AWESOME songs and I was surprised they didnt do the same set list as West Palm Beach. Drove 5 and a half hours there through ORLANDO TRAFFIC and trust me... IT WAS WORTH IT!]]></comment>
<comment author="Sam" timestamp="6:55 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[Completely amazing. The camera on Thom's Piano that he sings into during You and Whose Army is bloody genius. "Dedicated to the folks on the hill."

I had an absolutely amazing time and will be seeing them again at Lollapalooza.]]></comment>
<comment author="Nick" timestamp="2:03 PM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure I heard at least a bit of "Sit down Stand up"
I don't rember if they played the whole song, but I know I heard the lyrics: The raindops/the raindrops....
Might have been during the Gloaming, but I'm a little foggy about the order.

All I know is that it was an amazing show.]]></comment>
<comment author="tampatrader" timestamp="11:28 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[was an amazing show.  granted, I was in the second row, center stage.  the setlist was phenomenal, the band was spot on all night.  the tourist was the highlight of the evening for me.  was so great to hear that song.  thom's mugging for the camera on you and whose army was reminicent of when he did that 5 years ago in WPB.  also hearing the bends was a huge surprise.  probably was the best show i've ever been to.]]></comment>
<comment author="sharky" timestamp="11:11 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[tf3,
I was in sec 6 it's not the venue it's the bands sound comp. & the way they hang the system they actually needed a bigger system. I've seen pleanty of shows there that sound just fine for a shed.]]></comment>
<comment author="tf3" timestamp="7:52 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[Sharky, I said same to my wife when we were sitting in our seats (section 8).  Guess what?  up on the lawn, sound was much better.  Visuals too.  The difference b/w the seats and the lawn at that venue is like being at 2 completely different concerts.  (I'll never buy seats there again!)  As for the band, first show here, amazing.  I would really like to hear them take off on an extended jam, for say 20 minutes.  Johnny would melt our brains!]]></comment>
<comment author="Daniel" timestamp="6:20 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[To me, this show raised the bar in all aspects (visuals, perfect sound, etc). I've seen the band 3 times before and this show was WAY past my expectations. The crowd in sect 14 was AMAZING and totally into the show. Beautiful night, great song choice, no complaints (except for the $40 enviro-friendly tshirts...too high for me....$10 poster is excellent thogh).]]></comment>
<comment author="Jason" timestamp="6:08 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[First time seeing Radiohead and it was awesome...These guys are some of the best muscians I've ever seen.]]></comment>
<comment author="sharky" timestamp="5:57 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[O'yah forgot the light show was amazing. Truly unique 100% LED lighting. Very cool.]]></comment>
<comment author="sharky" timestamp="5:39 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[The show was fair for them it didn't get going until Optimistic. I did have a good time thou a fair show by them is still better than most bands.
The last tour threw FL the West Palm show now that was amazing. The sound was really low that would have helped the talkers when I can talk to my wife at a normal level somethings wrong plus it would have helped the energy. Still a good time for a Tues.,]]></comment>
<comment author="SHiTZ" timestamp="1:09 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 07, 2008"><![CDATA[yeah the crowd sucked but thats just tampa in general. its a city of displaced frat-boy deuche bags and stupid bleached skanks. radiohead however was absolutely phenomenal. musically probably the best show i've ever seen. thom sounded great and the band was dead on. "you and whose army" never sounded so amazing.   ]]></comment>
<comment author="jef" timestamp="11:37 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 06, 2008"><![CDATA[Phenomenal show.  This is a very special band. To hear this kind of music is deep.  The big amphitheater takes away from these guys.  If you didn't like it, you're not getting it.  Not everybody does.  Did anybody see the person in a bear costume during videotape?  I was 5th row, section 14.  The guy next to me pointed it out it out on the path between the single and double digit sections, but it was too late.  I only caught the back side of this inconspicuous, fluffy white bear on two legs.  What fun!]]></comment>
<comment author="Matt" timestamp="11:12 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 06, 2008"><![CDATA[Yeah, I was probably one of those douchebags that was singing loud enough to piss the people off all around me, but ya know what? I don't care. It was my first time seeing Radiohead, probably going to be my last and id have been damned if I didnt sing my heart out.

AMAZING SHOW!]]></comment>
<comment author="Jason" timestamp="10:03 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 06, 2008"><![CDATA[I agree. One of the worst crowds ever. Had to tell the a-hole next to me (that was sitting in my seats after my friend and I got back from the bathroom) to get off of his phone as he was shouting pretty much right into my ear. I had seats in the VIP section (SEC 9) and the most annoying freaks kept coming in there trying to "score the raddest seats" as I overheard. Radiohead were everything I thought they would be though: amazing. ]]></comment>
<comment author="Ron DeLucia" timestamp="9:50 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 06, 2008"><![CDATA[One of these days I'll catch Spinning Plates... I was too early in the Amnesiac tour (Stone Mountain... I heard they sound checked it there) for it, but have been hoping one of the tours since would bring it by.]]></comment>
<comment author="Anthony " timestamp="8:52 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 06, 2008"><![CDATA[Radiohead was amazing. The crowd sucked. Thanks to the stupid hippie next to me, who spilled beer on my fiancee and talked the entire show! He said he has seen them 23 times, so he decided to talk through NUDE and I could not even hear. thanks for making my first time seeing radiohead the WORST CONCERT I HAVE EVER BEEN TO!!!!!!!!!!]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=621]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
