<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="2"><![CDATA[Washington]]></locale>
<city id="169"><![CDATA[Auburn]]></city>
<venue id="287"><![CDATA[White River Amphiteatre]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>White+River+Amphiteatre</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Wednesday, August 20, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>659</previousshow>
<nextshow>661</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="3" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="4" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="5" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="6" id="49"><![CDATA[Pyramid Song]]></track>
<track num="7" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="8" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="9" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="10" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="11" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="12" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="13" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="14" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="15" id="54"><![CDATA[Dollars & Cents]]></track>
<track num="16" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="41"><![CDATA[How To Disappear Completely]]></track>
<track num="19" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="20" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="21" id="44"><![CDATA[In Limbo]]></track>
<track num="22" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="24" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="25" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[adelaney]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Vancouver]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Madam Curie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[randyrad]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[daviddi33]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Evolo]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[el presidente]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jaytab]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Petersill]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[entheogen111]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[(*disco*)]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[redsoxfaan3]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[wmgaretjax]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[murmurs13]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[stevenstrange51]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[CaptainFloyd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ebot]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<comments>
<comment author="akrh" timestamp="11:54 PM [PST], Friday, August 22, 2008"><![CDATA[in limbo hasnt been played in nearly 5 years!
pyramid song was astounding!  thom was in a way better mood than in vancouver
The Seattle crowd was mature, whereas vancouver was young.
personally I prefer fans who r respectfull!
thom said it best in Vancouver ,"settle down boys, this aint no fuckup rage against the machine show"!]]></comment>
<comment author="Petersill" timestamp="9:50 PM [PST], Friday, August 22, 2008"><![CDATA[Not their most memorable show but definately worth every mile driven, every dollar spent, and every moment waiting.  Nothing really tops a Radiohead show at the Hollywood Bowl but hearing Pyramid Song and Climbing Up the Walls was pretty chilling. It was special to be about 20 feet from Johnny Greenwood.  Would love to hear them mix up sets with songs like You, Glass House, Trickster and I swear I would never go to another concert again if they finished their shows with Blow Out again like the YouTube version they have from 1994 at the Astoria. Holy Fuck that would let me die a happy kid. Til next show.

PS Seattle crowds do suck.]]></comment>
<comment author="Mike" timestamp="10:46 AM [PST], Friday, August 22, 2008"><![CDATA[After the first false start of Faust Arp, Thom and Jonny broke into Tell Me Why by Neil Young, at least until Thom forgot the words to that too, which didn't take very long.]]></comment>
<comment author="justin" timestamp="4:51 PM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[please tell me what electronic beats were playing before radiohead took stage.  it seemed as if it were one album that played the duration that followed after liars took the stage and the roadie crew setup for radiohead.  i tried to tag it with shazam, but i couldn't get a signal...  will someone please come to my aid and tell me what was playing?!?]]></comment>
<comment author="gratefuldan" timestamp="3:00 PM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[OH 
FORGOT to mention TALK SHOW HOST...OMFG!
AWESOME!]]></comment>
<comment author="gratefuldan" timestamp="2:52 PM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[Triple start Faust Arp!!!  SOOOO glad Thom kept going!
As everyone else mentioned...this show was KICK ASS!
Thom was dancing all over, and really goating us during You and Whose Army!
It took 3-1/2 hours to get out of the parking lot though!!]]></comment>
<comment author="jaytab" timestamp="2:29 PM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[I think I'm going to have to rank this as the lowest of the three Radiohead shows I've seen.  I didn't feel like the band ever really reached the intense level of energy Ive seen them get into in the past on stage.  It also didn't help, and probably contributed to, the lackluster response from the crowd.  It was another typical Seattle show where everyone stands in one place and might, just might, move their head a bit or shift their weight.

Don't get me wrong--I thought the show was fantastic overall.  Once again they had awesome lighting and visual effects.  And I think one of the best things about any Radiohead show is listening to an album and thinking, "they can't do this live..." and then watching them do it.  The band certainly seemed to be having a good time and that definitely helps.  From the pit I thought the sound was pretty good, although maybe a bit bass-heavy.  I also wish they would have thrown in a few more older songs to mix it up a bit more--and possibly raise the energy level.

And as far as making any show a good experience at White River, take the alternate routes suggested on http://www.rivergiver.com -- I took the back way via SR169 and drove all the way to the venue and spent more time stopped at traffic lights on the way than in any kind of line.  I would also highly recommend giving in and buying the Premium Parking pass, unless you enjoy sitting in a parking lot until 1AM.  It sucks but the rest of their parking lot and parking staff are totally worthless.

Of course despite any shortcomings of the show, Ill absolutely stay up all night again to get tickets for the next show.
]]></comment>
<comment author="Eric Con Queso" timestamp="12:44 PM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[First Radiohead show.  Lived up to all expectations.  The light show especially blew me away--I wasn't expecting anything that could take me away from the screens of the band playing, however the set did just that (especially on Idioteque).  I was out on the lawn, which was a little more mellow than I wouldn've liked...however every song they played sounded better than the album versions.....which again I did not expect.  Can't wait to see them next time they come around...hopefully it'll be dryer for those that had to be on the lawn.  Great to see Nigel!]]></comment>
<comment author="n-dawg" timestamp="11:00 AM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[So sublime. "Optimistic" was like Sugar Ray Leonard in his punchy prime. "Pyramid" swooned. "National Anthem" roared, and "Lucky" soared. "How to Disappear" was gorgeous, and "In Limbo" was a tasty treat. The look on Yorke's face during "You and Whose Army" personified the song perfectly. A wonderful show.]]></comment>
<comment author="Hogger" timestamp="10:04 AM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[the rains followed the band again, but most of the venue is covered.. Special moments included reckoner (one day I want to hear that gorge version again), There There,Talk show, Lucky, No Surprises, Jigsaw and that grand little jam that they kept somewhat intentionally fucking up...
A note on Atmosphere:  Seattle crowds are dull!  The greatest rock band in the world is in town and you come to sit or stand for 2 hours.
It took more than 2 hours to get to the venue from Seattle!  There must be an easier way!]]></comment>
<comment author="Aliam" timestamp="9:51 AM [PST], Thursday, August 21, 2008"><![CDATA[Show was flawless, even when the rain at the end!! I've always dreamed of seeing Climbing up the Walls live and on this tour I knew I had a chance! Thom was captivating and inspiring, as always! ~Radiohead does not disappoint!]]></comment>
<comment author="jlowe" timestamp="11:53 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 20, 2008"><![CDATA[Despite the show being sold out, people were walking up to the ticket booth and buying seats up close and in the Pitt. Meanwhile    Im holding my back row tickets that I purchased way back in April the first hour they went on sale. Not fair.

But they played Talk Show Host so why am I complaining about anything.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=660]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
