<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="118"><![CDATA[North Carolina]]></locale>
<city id="226"><![CDATA[Charlotte]]></city>
<venue id="469"><![CDATA[Verizon Wireless Amphitheatre]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Verizon+Wireless+Amphitheatre</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Friday, May 09, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="11"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Spring) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>622</previousshow>
<nextshow>624</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Liars]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="2" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="3" id="29"><![CDATA[Airbag]]></track>
<track num="4" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="5" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="6" id="60"><![CDATA[Sail To The Moon]]></track>
<track num="7" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="8" id="89"><![CDATA[Myxomatosis]]></track>
<track num="9" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="10" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="11" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="12" id="43"><![CDATA[Optimistic]]></track>
<track num="13" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="14" id="51"><![CDATA[You And Whose Army?]]></track>
<track num="15" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
<track num="16" id="156"><![CDATA[Bangers and Mash]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="162"><![CDATA[Go Slowly]]></track>
<track num="19" id="58"><![CDATA[Talk Show Host]]></track>
<track num="20" id="4"><![CDATA[Exit Music (for a film)]]></track>
<track num="21" id="16"><![CDATA[Planet Telex]]></track>
<track num="22" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="30"><![CDATA[Paranoid Android]]></track>
<track num="24" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[tenacious z]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chashollywood]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Madam Curie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[little_rowboat]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chules]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ATLFalconsFAN]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[pj10]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bobcat34]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[clay]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[inourhands]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[makacu]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dustbunny]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[le]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[705eye]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ruddtherudd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[aroach]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[talkshowhost]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Arianna]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Copperdog]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Slayer13]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Wicked_Molasses]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[harri]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[miked.]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Zombe]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radioheaddhs]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[grobie1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[emagdnim015]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[masuther]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[babysgotthebends]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[rdiohd]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lanora]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[quadrophenia]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[grobie07]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[gloamdroid57]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[bengrobe1]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chipymac]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[Soundcheck consisted of:<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=16">Planet Telex</a> (twice),<br /> 
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=28">Punch Up At a Wedding</a>, <br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=60">Sail to the Moon</a> (twice),<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=157">Jigsaw Falling into Place</a> (four times),<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=61">There There</a>,<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=158">15 Step</a>,<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=137">The Gloaming</a>,<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=162">Go Slowly</a> (twice),<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=89">Myxomatosis</a>,<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=45">Idioteque</a>,<br />
<a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=156">Bangers and Mash</a>,<br />
and <a href="/58_trackDetails.php?trackID=154">Bodysnatchers</a>.
]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="Alan Welch" timestamp="7:33 PM [PST], Wednesday, September 17, 2008"><![CDATA[Six Words...WHERE I END AND YOU BEGIN!!!!!!!!

Truly amazing show. I wish I could blow many thousands of dollars so that I may see them at every show.]]></comment>
<comment author="glen burnie" timestamp="9:02 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 14, 2008"><![CDATA[the show was enchanting, as expected.  But what is up with all the dumb assholes talking on cell phones and trying to take pictures from three miles away.  If you are going to bring in a digital camera--PLEASE--cover up the back so others don't have to be distracted.  The guy in front of me was browsing through his whole (digi)photo album trying to find pictures not worthy of keeping so he can take more pictures not worthy of keeping.  He looked at me like I was crazy, when I told him, "I really like your pictures, but can I look at them AFTER the show."  At least he and his girlfriend got up and left.  Technology gives us Radiohead and jerk-offs.  It's a fair trade-off, I guess.]]></comment>
<comment author="ac" timestamp="8:47 AM [PST], Wednesday, May 14, 2008"><![CDATA[The show was great...and didn't seem short at all.  The traffic was indeed HORRENDOUS!  We drove up an exit to get gas (we were on dead empty and didn't feel like pushing our car to the show) and then hit it from the opposite direction, but it turned out the theatre parking was right there, so there was no need to turn around.  We entered the back of the amphitheatre right as the first few notes were played.  There definitely needs to be a better system for parking.  Our seats were in the back of the reserved, but we made it down half way and entered in on the side (stage left)  Until we moved more central, I thought the sound was kind of weak (but I think they didn't have the speakers pointed outward).  

I'll agree; The lights were great.  But NOWHERE NEAR a Chris Koruda powered light spectacle ala PHISH!  I walked up front after the crowd cleared out to get a better look at what the lighting devices were.  They pretty much looked like linked fluorescent tubes from where I was sitting, but upon closer inspection (and not trying to get tossed) I saw that they were some type of metal or plastic with indentations on the side.  

As for the music...once we moved more central, it sounded great.  The band was having fun and seemed generally excited to be back out on tour.  As usual, the bass lines were incredible and a little funk had me groovin'. I would have loved to have seen another show or two, but sadly I am now working for the man and vacations are hard to come by.  MEZMIRIZING!
]]></comment>
<comment author="heddie" timestamp="4:28 PM [PST], Tuesday, May 13, 2008"><![CDATA[awesome show i was right at the very front in the pit...i am too sad that it is over hoping to catch them on the second leg of the us tour, where i end and you begin was my fave]]></comment>
<comment author="Joel" timestamp="10:14 AM [PST], Tuesday, May 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Great Show, but traffic was unacceptable. It took us 2hours to get into the lot and 1.5 hour to get out...we missed the first 2 songs because of it...did anybody else think the show was kinna short?]]></comment>
<comment author="aroach" timestamp="6:35 PM [PST], Monday, May 12, 2008"><![CDATA[Great show.  The band was in top form and the added light show from the passing storm made for a memorable evening.  The new album comes off well live.  The Talk Show Host into Exit Music was pretty special.  Good crowd and vibe.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="Colin Allen" timestamp="10:48 PM [PST], Sunday, May 11, 2008"><![CDATA[So good I had a hard time sleeping the next 2 nights. They really know the energy of their fans and know how to mix up the song selection in order to please everyone. I would kill to see them again soon!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="dru" timestamp="1:03 AM [PST], Sunday, May 11, 2008"><![CDATA[Absolutely the greatest light and visual show ever! I felt like I was playing Simon all night! ]]></comment>
<comment author="Banks Smither" timestamp="4:35 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[Was in the pit with only about 500 people or less, the whole place was about 20,000 people.  Thom was energetic and they played Sail to the Moon for NC for voting for Obama or at least that was my take.  Great show wish I could seem them again on this tour cause the In Rainbows stuff is really good live.  ]]></comment>
<comment author="jml" timestamp="4:24 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[GREAT SHOW!! caught them two years ago at Bonnaroo. The light show was phenomenal as well as the lightning going on in the sky. It rained when the sky was actually clear. Sail to the Moon and Morning Bell were fantastic to hear but I never expected to hear 4 out of 7 album-opening songs in one night. THANKS!]]></comment>
<comment author="Patrick" timestamp="4:14 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[Can't believe they played talk show host.  My favorite song and a very rare treat.  First show and I was on the lawn.  Couldn't see too much, but thank God for the light show.      ]]></comment>
<comment author="tronner" timestamp="4:09 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[great show...my grandma's band is louder than that shit I saw last night.  Bring the volume!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="fan" timestamp="12:54 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[MYXOMATOSIS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="Will" timestamp="12:00 PM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[Absolutely incredible show. Myxomatosis was an awesome surprise, and it was one of the best songs of the show. Other candidates include 15 Step, Weird Fishes/Arpeggi, Idioteque, Bangers and Mash, Planet Telex, and Paranoid Android. Just all around incredible... Thom's little charade with the camera during You and Whose Army? was absolutely amazing. They played Talk Show Host, and I'm going to be honest... I'd never heard it before. Where did that come from?]]></comment>
<comment author="A" timestamp="11:38 AM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[This concert can be called nothing less than Epic. Truly epic. It got more spectacular as the songs progressed. it was amazing when they played Sail to the Moon, unexpected, and the lighting was glorious. Not to mention Thom's dancing was adorable]]></comment>
<comment author="bob" timestamp="7:52 AM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[What a great show. There was a passing lighning storm right before Liars started so we stayed in the lot and missed them. Luckily, we missed a downpour. Seats in Section 6 were great... center, covered. The crowd was great, too. You could tell they were all there for the music.

Everyone has their favorites they want to hear and we got several. Sail to the Moon, Myxamatosis... we were feeling lucky. My brother had been wanting them to play Go Slowly, which I couldn't even place. He was freaking when they started that. But then Planet Telex blew us away. That might have been my favorite song of the night. The light show is amazing. This was really one of the best shows I've ever seen. Ok, my only negative was that Jonny's guitar was a little too quiet on a couple songs, especially Paranoid Android.

With all the electronic stuff they do on records it's great to see them live and be reminded that they're still all about the guitar and they still want to rock. Brilliant show.]]></comment>
<comment author="Matt" timestamp="6:42 AM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[This is the only show so far where they played Planet Telex...the lighting was AMAZING and I'm so glad that I got to see it.  Wish we hadn't missed Lucky and Just though :(]]></comment>
<comment author="Steve" timestamp="5:30 AM [PST], Saturday, May 10, 2008"><![CDATA[First Radiohead show....  Had a blast. One of the coolest stage light shows since Floyd. Sound was clean and crispp. Better than I had hoped.]]></comment>
<comment author="andy martin" timestamp="11:13 PM [PST], Friday, May 09, 2008"><![CDATA[SAIL TO THE MOON!!! WOO HOO! I HOPE THEY PLAY THAT WHEN I SEE THEM IN AUGUST!!! SO GOOD, SO GOOD!!!]]></comment>
<comment author="MT" timestamp="7:07 PM [PST], Monday, May 05, 2008"><![CDATA[I have two extra tickets for sale (face value) for this show...section 5.  I hope to get them in someone's hands that will enjoy them and not a scalper.]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=623]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
