<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rdata>
<breadcrumb>
<country id="1"><![CDATA[USA]]></country>
<locale id="25"><![CDATA[New Jersey]]></locale>
<city id="153"><![CDATA[Camden]]></city>
<venue id="481"><![CDATA[Susquehanna Bank Center]]></venue>
</breadcrumb>
<flashlabel>
<venue>Susquehanna+Bank+Center</venue>
</flashlabel>
<showdate>Tuesday, August 12, 2008</showdate>
<tour id="13"><![CDATA[North America 2008 (Summer) In Rainbows]]></tour>
<shownavi><previousshow>654</previousshow>
<nextshow>657</nextshow>
</shownavi>
<support><![CDATA[Grizzly Bear]]></support>
<setlist>
<main>
<track num="1" id="158"><![CDATA[15 Step]]></track>
<track num="2" id="61"><![CDATA[There There]]></track>
<track num="3" id="46"><![CDATA[Morning Bell]]></track>
<track num="4" id="166"><![CDATA[All I Need]]></track>
<track num="5" id="40"><![CDATA[National Anthem]]></track>
<track num="6" id="164"><![CDATA[Videotape]]></track>
<track num="7" id="153"><![CDATA[Weird Fishes/Arpeggi]]></track>
<track num="8" id="137"><![CDATA[The Gloaming]]></track>
<track num="9" id="95"><![CDATA[Where I End and You Begin]]></track>
<track num="10" id="167"><![CDATA[Faust Arp]]></track>
<track num="11" id="35"><![CDATA[No Surprises]]></track>
<track num="12" id="157"><![CDATA[Jigsaw Falling Into Place]]></track>
<track num="13" id="17"><![CDATA[The Bends]]></track>
<track num="14" id="45"><![CDATA[Idioteque]]></track>
<track num="15" id="34"><![CDATA[Climbing Up The Walls]]></track>
<track num="16" id="65"><![CDATA[Nude]]></track>
<track num="17" id="154"><![CDATA[Bodysnatchers]]></track>
</main>
<encore1>
<track num="18" id="160"><![CDATA[House of Cards]]></track>
<track num="19" id="36"><![CDATA[Lucky]]></track>
<track num="20" id="162"><![CDATA[Go Slowly]]></track>
<track num="21" id="22"><![CDATA[Just]]></track>
<track num="22" id="27"><![CDATA[Street Spirit (fade out)]]></track>
</encore1>
<encore2>
<track num="23" id="116"><![CDATA[Reckoner]]></track>
<track num="24" id="16"><![CDATA[Planet Telex]]></track>
<track num="25" id="38"><![CDATA[Everything In Its Right Place]]></track>
</encore2>
</setlist>
<memberspresent>
<member id=""><![CDATA[crp640]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ATH14]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radiohokie]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jindew2]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[OMS]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[okcokc]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[leifdog222]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[chipster]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Strummer]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Bylimb]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[trojanpony]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[gberg]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[geeveebee]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[ryguy469]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[StormDawg]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Blake]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[blazak]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[one_after909]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[mattison1980]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[dankgirl713]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sweetcell]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[masuther]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[relaxing]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[radio_head]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[sometimesnj]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[lanora]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[binky the doormat]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[siege72]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Kid Julian]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[nickA]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[luxamnesiac]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[naivemelody]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Dragula22]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Idaa]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[jordan]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[acmarsh5]]></member>
<member id=""><![CDATA[Blake911]]></member>
</memberspresent>
<shownotes><![CDATA[ ]]></shownotes>
<comments>
<comment author="Lindsay" timestamp="6:43 PM [PST], Friday, August 22, 2008"><![CDATA[This is my third time seeing them (03 and 06 being other times), and I thought they were amazing.  They always seem to pull out a few songs you don't really expect, and that is one of the things that makes their shows so great--you get all that new stuff, but then there's an old favorite or two thrown in.  I'm surprised I've seen negative comments in several places about this show... I mean, I might have been cranky had I been on the lawn, but I had good seats and was just completely absorbed in the light show and the music and the experience.  Definitely not disappointed at all.  I think the only thing that has me down is that I can't find a bootleg of the show... I still listen to Camden'03 on my iPod a lot.]]></comment>
<comment author="Mark" timestamp="6:15 AM [PST], Tuesday, August 19, 2008"><![CDATA[Personally, I thought the sound was a little off.  Hard to believe their show a few years ago at the SkyDome had better sound quality.  I loved There There, The Gloaming, and the ending on Everything in It's Right Place was great.  The play list was interesting - almost like they put all their CDs in a CD player and put it on 'random'.  Gotta admit, there were a few on the set list I would not have chosen ...]]></comment>
<comment author="kxw" timestamp="10:08 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[yeah...about the videotape remix. it was....different. i loved it, dont get me wrong, but i thought the added bass drum in the beginning took away from the simplicity of the song, which is what makes it so great. the band actually experimented alot with that song, adding all kinds of effects. then one day before thom got to practice, the band stripped it down to its core and they realized how much of a masterpiece it was just like that. still good live tho]]></comment>
<comment author="Daano81" timestamp="1:14 PM [PST], Thursday, August 14, 2008"><![CDATA[Great concert!!! Music selection was awesome especially everything from The Bends (the album that got most of us into Radiohead in the first place).  I'm surprised no one has said anything about the new mix for Videotape, which is as beautiful a song live as it is on the album.  I'd love to hear them in a smaller venue...the lawn is just too far away from the action on the stage.]]></comment>
<comment author="Melis" timestamp="5:52 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[The concert was amaziiiing. I've been waiting to see Radiohead for years now, and they're my favorite band ever. The concert was everything I expected, even better. The light shows were phenomenal and Thom's crazy alien dances were so much fun! I know that they didn't play their top hit songs (personally I really hoped that they'd play 2+2=5) the other songs were absolutely amazing! I hope they will come back soon in 1-2 years.]]></comment>
<comment author="kxw" timestamp="5:30 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[i am a huge radiohead fan and i have wanted to see them ever since i first heard their music. all i can say is that in no way was i dissapointed. amazing. absolutely amazing. i especially liked thom dancing frantically to idioteque, the semi-rocked out version of jigsaw, and the insanely amazing just. then again, i could say something good about pretty much every song that they played. as for the venue, although the acoustics werent flawless, it was a million percent better than the last concert i went to, at the wachovia center. i think in terms of actual skill, radiohead is an average band, but the reason why we all love them so much is for their pure musicality and overall musical genius. they have a way of making you feel the music in a way you never thought possible, and for that, radiohead is king.]]></comment>
<comment author="ben" timestamp="4:55 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[I've been waiting to see Radiohead for several years now and they delivered on everything I expected, even in such a large venue that doesn't always convey a band's strengths very well. Most of the songs from In Rainbows came across with a lot more power than I had expected and fit in with the rest of the show well enough. I was giddy to hear songs like Lucky and Idioteque that really got the crowd into the show. They might have leaned a little heavily on The Bends material, but it's great for a concert like that to have some hard-rocking songs. The light show was spectacular to watch, especially since I was on the lawn and could barely see the band. All in all, an excellent show from an excellent band.]]></comment>
<comment author="Blake" timestamp="3:26 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my second Radiohead showand it was INCREDIBLE. Im still in a complete state of euphoria from last night!  While a bit heavy on In Rainbows material, the setlist was more than satisfying.  Radiohead opted to rock out, playing FOUR songs from the bends while cutting out some of their more cerebral tracks from the Kid A/Amnesiac era. They played an interesting remix of The Gloamingwith Thom dancing chaotically during intermittent, guitar-heavy breaks in the main flow of the song. The live version of Lucky, complete with an intense blazing orange lightshow was extraordinary!  No Surprises was a pleasant surprise but my favorite moment of the night had to be the explosive Idioteque coupled with schizophrenic blinking LEDs.  

I heard a collective groan from the crowd when Radiohead played the first few notes of Go Slowly during the first encore hahaha.  I couldnt disagree more with the crowd.  This song has really grown on me and I enjoyed the live rendition immensely. 

My only complaint of the night was in Radioheads performance of All I Need (which in my opinion is the standout track of In Rainbows)---the song seemed a bit uninspired/languid but other than that the show was perfect.

Apparently, the band sound checked In Limbo (my all-time favorite Radiohead track) before the show. But alas..It was not meant to be.
]]></comment>
<comment author="Casey" timestamp="1:17 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[I'd been waiting many years to see Radiohead and I was not at all disappointed by what I saw last night. The thing about a band like Radiohead is that they are so prolific, and so consistent, that for every song you were happy to hear there's at least one other song you wish they would play. There's no making everyone happy. My expectations were matched if not exceeded.]]></comment>
<comment author="Strummer" timestamp="12:26 PM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[This was my first Radiohead show and overall I thought it was amazing.  I was surprised that the band could pull off their such intricate music live as well as having the best light show I've seen at a concert.  Although I really wanted to hear 2+2=5, Exit Music or Paranoid Android, songs like Bodysnatchers, Idioteque and Just sounded amazing.  I love what Radiohead is doing.  They are one of the only bands that are keeping music alive nowadays and I hope they come back next year.]]></comment>
<comment author="josh" timestamp="11:37 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[no offense intended but to those who have been complaining about hearing in rainbows every show, they're following the same format they've followed for years when it comes to new album tracks being played live, as for "boring, plodding, and unimaginative setlists" this one isn't really that different from any other night, did it really suprise anyone that they played there there early and closed with everything? i'm actually glad they didn't do PA and karma for once. radiohead isn't really known for making radical changes to their sets, they rarely even play their b-sides live, if you didn't appreciate this show you were expecting something other than radiohead, sound quality did kinda suck though but honestly i dont remember a show at that venue where the sound was anything other than average]]></comment>
<comment author="Jake" timestamp="11:15 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Wow Paul, and PD?  I wasnt at the show but how can a show that includes Planet Telax, Just, The Bends, National Anthem,  and WIEAYB, slow.  It's not often that Radiohead plays all those songs in one set.]]></comment>
<comment author="VaTechDCman" timestamp="11:08 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[This concert was a perfect example of a band at the top of their game. I sat in the reserved section and hope that those sitting on the lawn were able to see just how amazing the stage setup and light show was as it played out through the night. I drove up from DC to see this--having missed the stormy show at Nissan Pavilion in May--and can say it was worth the wait, and every mile in between. BRAVO!]]></comment>
<comment author="Gary" timestamp="10:56 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Great show, solid A-.  Band was tight, and the light show amazing.  Would have liked to hear "Pyramid Song" or "Dollars & Cents".  "The Gloaming" and "Go Slowly" are nice songs, just not good *concert* songs, not the kind that'll get a huge crowd like that going.]]></comment>
<comment author="Paul" timestamp="9:51 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[I agree completely with PD. Set list was slow and plodding and it felt like there were 5 ballads in a row. Grizzly Bear was more asswhopping at times. 

Let's be clear - the overall show was still phenomenal, the lights were unreal and thom sounded angelic. A bit too clean...

No Amnesiac tracks at all.

I could nitpick for days, overall I had a great time, just felt set list was a lil bland.]]></comment>
<comment author="karma_police" timestamp="8:56 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[amazing!! they pretty much played the best songs off every album.. best show i've seen in a LONG time!!]]></comment>
<comment author="Pops" timestamp="8:36 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Sat right near the mixing board and got to see Andy "the Lighting guy" perform. Wow!
Great set list, great renditions, great visuals. Thom was in voice, top shelf all of the way.]]></comment>
<comment author="PD" timestamp="8:03 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Actually, this was a disappointing show. The sound quality was mediocre and the set list was plodding and unimaginative. When Tom grabbed the acoustic and said he was going to do one for those of us on the lawn, I was hoping for "Exit Music" or "Fake Plastic Trees". "Go Slowly" was a drag. Is anyone else tired of them playing ALL of "In Rainbows" at every show? Great album but mix it up a little, boys. I give this show a B minus. ]]></comment>
<comment author="newestbigradiofan" timestamp="7:53 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[last night was my first radiohead show and i absolutely loved it. the whole show was insane. They   rocked the place last night. I don't think there was a person there that will forget last night's show anytime soon.]]></comment>
<comment author="Amanda" timestamp="7:49 AM [PST], Wednesday, August 13, 2008"><![CDATA[Great show! Ended up getting to sit in reserved, everyone was really into it. Highlights: national anthem, climbing up the walls, idioteque, bodysnatchers, LUCKY, just, reckoner, planet telex!, everything in its right place. haha that's almost everything]]></comment>
</comments>
<post_comments><![CDATA[post_comments.php?showID=656]]></post_comments>
<getall_comments><![CDATA[&allComments=1]]></getall_comments>
</rdata>
